Open, open stream
So, with that said,
Today we have 3 Japanese speakers,
4 English speakers,
3 English speakers,
1 Indonesian speaker—sorry!
Sorry!
Close one, close one!
Whether it's Japanese or Indonesian,
or even English, Zeta-chan here
can speak them all, but
today,
together with Team Kaze
and those who will be playing Super Smash Bros.,
we’re going to play 300% Super Smash Bros.
and have some fun!
So, with that said,
let’s start with introductions first.
Sound check and
well then,
Kari, please go ahead.
Hello everyone! It's me, Mori Kurai--P from Hololive
English Myth! Let's have fun!
Let's enjoy! Enjoy, enjoy!
Alright, Gigi,
everyone,
It's me,
Hololive's
Ingrid Justice,
Gigi Mo Nin,
Far Feaster, yo!
Yay!
Please, okayu~
Yes, munch munch, okayu~
I'm Nekomata Okayu from Hololive Gamers.
Today I haven't played Smash in forever,
so please go easy on me!
Yeah!
Well then,
Not Beginner or Not Beginner...
Seriously though, I'm totally bad at it!
With Smash, I'm genuinely either really good or really bad.
Definitely skilled, maybe! Yay!
Alright, so then,
next up is Shiori.
Ah, Shiorin!
This is Shiorin's Bella.
Your servant, so please enjoy the Hololive archive!
Oh, nice! Please take care of me!
Nemu nemu
Thanks, okay?
Yes.
Then, Zeta,
Aaami shan stand!
Hello!
I'm a total beginner.
Everyone, please be kind to me!
Don't worry!
Toa just installed it a moment ago too,
so same here.
Yes.
Then Fubu-chan, please go ahead.
Yes, Fubu King Krule here.
Nice to meet you all!
Fubu King Krule, that's right.
We'll be going with Fubu King Krule,
so please take care of me!
Yes.
Thank you very much! Yes.
So, with that said,
Kon'yappi and Wasabi here! Yes!
Thank you very much!
Seriously,
we're real beginners, so
I hope we can just have fun today.
Today only investigators showed up, huh?
Well then,
what should we do? Who fights? Alright, alright,
let's start with the first match.
Do your best!
Scary! Come on, get up, get up!
Scary, scary, scary!
Come on
Come on, hurry up
If nobody's going up
What the hell? Hurry up!
Come on, come on
Come on, nice
Nice
Two more people
Two more
Nice
Nice, one more
Woof woof
Pichu, catch, catch, oh!
Nice! We won!
Octabby, together!
Double Kirby
Pichu
I don't get how to do it
Sorry
I'm Black Kirby—huh? Black Kirby?
Wait a sec
Oh no, oh no
How do I fly?
That's amazing
Shiorin-san
Hold on
Oh no
Okaeri-san
Neta Samado-chan, this is bad
Shiorin-san, the Halberd—huh?
Wait a moment
Shiorin-san
Shiorin-san, I died
With Okaeri-san
With Okaeri-san—it's scary! No way!
That's strong
This is strong
Do your best—quickly! It's decided
Congratulations—you're strong
I got killed twice by Shiori
Shiori
Strong
Then let's switch next
Let's switch
Then do your best
Jiji and Zeta, and
Fugu-chan and one more person—let's go
Then let's go with Towa—okay
Let's go
Ah, Steve
Steve
Wasn't Steve supposed to be strong?
Steve is a power character
Clever
Steve appearing here is unexpected
That's really dangerous
I am Steve
I am Steve—what's this?
What's this?
Wait, wait, wait, wait
Jijii, stop it
Jijii, hold on
Wait a sec, Jijii, stop it
Stop it
That's not it
Team Fu, do your best—wait!
It already hurts—so intense
Super Minecraft-like
Is that Jaita's HP?
We need to explain the HP settings
Yeah
An incredibly active stage
Ah, ah, ow
Fubu-chan, can you even do it?
Fubu-chan, can you even do it? That
Hey
Huh? Why are you so yellow?
Huh? Why are both of you super yellow?
Yellow
It's yellow—grabbed the coin, then ouch
Nice
Did it, did it—nice
Zenta
Let's go
Go Mario
Mario's bouncing around
Bouncing around
Zenta's bouncing like crazy
Zenta jumping
The guard is usable too—that's seriously impressive.
You're actually using it well.
Is there a one-in-a-million chance?
This one exists! It exists!
Could it be...?
Back ring.
There it is—!
Amazing! Amazing!
What is this place?
What happens when you collect lots of coins?
How is Zetta even alive?
Zetta, starting from 0% like that...
Because we're starting fresh.
I just messed up the settings a bit.
The settings are messed up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah—it's fine.
I'll sort it out later.
Later.
We can adjust the settings later.
Let's fix the settings later.
It's getting a bit too strong.
So strong—
That...
Ah, I see it!
I laughed.
Um...
What's that? That character's strong. It's the bottom right.
Bottom right, bottom right.
From the character select screen...
You can change it from the character select.
Wait a sec.
Waiting for other players... Ah, fixed it! Fixed it!
This is definitely it.
Season 3 is short.
Isn't that not really true?
Totally normal.
Yeah, that's right.
Instead of Kirby...
Let's try Fox instead.
Nice! Let's try all sorts of characters.
Alright, 300%.
300%.
Good! Next one. Nice!
Nice!
Good! Next!
Old man, old man—go! I'm Steve.
I'm Steve. Nice!
Nice! Steve! Steve!
I hate Peach! Let's go!
It's Peach!
Peach! Peach!
Peach! Peach! Peach! So cute!
Team English! Let's go! Indeed, Team English!
Your Team English...
Turned into Yoshi.
Yoshi!
Here.
Sorry.
Strong! Sorry! Oh no!
Sorry! I want to do my best!
That's great.
Jiji is hiding.
Hiding Jiji.
It's One Vee Van!
Still going!
Are they crafting something?
They're making something, right?
You were doing great.
You're trying hard—strong!
You're getting stronger!
It's okay! It's okay!
Strong! Nice! Steve's the strongest!
Steve's strong!
Steve! Strong! Strong!
Na—
Ice fight!
Nice fight! Next!
Then shall we do it? Please go ahead.
So, the real match starts at 300% damage, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah—oh, I see!
So that's why you're practicing—I get it.
At 300%, each person fights twice—two rounds.
I see.
Fight twice until reaching 300% damage.
Well then...
Hunt Open is also included. End.
Wait—it's changing!
Pikachu
Pikachu is Pikomi's color—really!
This is strong
What is this?
It's been crazy the whole time
Pi
Kachuu, that's crazy
Crazy
Hunting is insane
Where'd it go?
The door
I was dead before I realized it
Pikachu
Crazy
Strong
So strong
Good
Delicious
Too good
It's decided, right?
Wait
Pikachu, Pikachu, Pikachu
Pikachu, strong Pikachu
Way too crazy
Hey, let me see your Pikachu for a sec—Pikachu looks good
Pikachu Pikachu is way too crazy
Pika Pika Festival
Is it turning into a Pika Fest?
Pika Fest
Pika Fest Pikachu Pikachu
Pikachu Pikachu
Let's decide with this
Ah, it's Steve
Steve's strong, huh
Steve again
What move is Pikachu using?
Which button?
Isn't it Thunder with Down+B?
Yes
Yeah, Pikachu
Down+B is
Vertical Thunder, right?
Like this, then C
I died myself though
TNT is insane
Wait a sec
First off, TNT
Wait a moment
Is Down+B like this?
Like this, right? Pikachu
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch
I killed myself
Upwards
Crazy, wait a sec
From 10 items like this, Pikachu
Pikachu, goodbye
Crazy
Ouch
It's Peach—Peach is strong
When someone wins
It's funny how that character suddenly seems strong
Korokoro
Nori-chan is strong, right?
Scary, scary—definitely strong
High-power Shiori
Haain
Well then
But Pikachu seems good
I just studied with Kano
Yeah, right?
Pikachu festival—let's go Pikachu!
This time, I
Roshyu—ah, sorry
Masked Pikachu
Looks strong, doesn't it?
King
Three Yoshis, three Yoshis
It's a pink Yoshi
Seems a bit off though
How do you use it? Where is it?
Guard is strong—Pika Pika
Was flying—way too strong!
Isn't this guy way too strong?
This guy?
As I thought, it's this King...
King K. Rool isn't here yet, you know, the one with all that nonsense.
King K. Rool!
What character is this? Is it Donkey Kong?
It's Donkey Kong!
Right, he's Donkey's boss.
If it's Donkey, maybe we can win?
Might actually work out!
Back when we fought Sephiroth and stuff...
He was strong!
Sephiroth's here!
Let's go with Sephiroth!
Sephiroth's weapon has such long reach!
Oh, really?
I haven't played FF7, but that's fine, right?
After trying out all kinds of characters...
You can join in too!
Go ahead, totally fine!
Even if you join multiple times in a row, it's okay!
Is Sephiroth scary or Donkey Kong—huh?
Mille!
Mille's here!
The gap between warrior gods is insane!
Way too insane!
Gigi, your face!
Face black!
Sam!
Undertale!
Huh?!
So big!
Long reach!
Let's go, Gigi!
Sans is strong—super strong!
Sephiroth looks like he has long reach too!
I can walk, but I can't run though...
Sephiroth!
Sans is amazing! Yay!
Strong!
While showing off...
I can smell it!
Go for it! Go for it!
Let's go!
What's this?
Awesome, Gigi!
Not Gigi—
Sans...
Sans' voice!
This...
Finding the right character really matters, huh.
Yeah!
Best Character Select!
You gotta find your best character, you guys.
I'm just picking randomly now.
I thought that's what everyone was doing.
You can randomly pick colors too—hold on...
Let me try!
Pika!
Nshuu!
Hey!
Father! Are there only seven characters?!
64—lol!
Go ahead, go ahead!
Sure thing!
This might be good!
Should I join?
What?
Whoa, Sephiroth took off his clothes—what is this?!
Off-screen Sephiroth!
Ugh, I hate this—it's pitch black!
Scary! So scary! What is this place?!
Mario!
There's no robot here!
Please, I wanna dig—ow! Sorry!
What is this place?
Oh no, it's Sephiroth calling!
All alone... another one!
Ah, apparently someone got trapped between them!
Whoa, stop it—!
There's always something inside trees, right?
I don't get it—wait, yeah, I get it!
There's always something inside trees, you know!
What happened?
It's gonna explode!
Inside the tree
Ah, that's amazing! So smart!
Towa's lack of character has been exposed
It'll open right away
Pretty much
Someone
Come on, come on!
Everyone's choosing different things
Alright, nice choice
Nice
Leave it to me—what is this robot?
Ah-wah, ah-wah-wah-wah
I knew you would make that joke. I was thinking it too. No way!
Stayway Brave, oh!
What is this? Ugh, what is this, seriously?
What is this?
I-way Stream Metal Frink
Why are you telling me this?
Whoa!
Ribgukob
Connect it
Robot
No way, no way!
No way, no way! Strong robot!
Get over here, geez, you know!
Dad, do we...?
Huh?
Oh!
Yay!
No!
Robo strong
Robo's so strong
Everyone's characters look strong
When you win, you know...
No shirt
Off-screen Sephiroth
Private Sephiroth
Private Jora, stop it!
You're kidding!
Sephiroth
At home, he doesn't wear clothes
Bayonetta
Oshiorizu character—so sexy
Bayonetta's cute
Sexy
Sexy Night Birdie
What is this place?
This...
It's Mother 3's garage
First, let's pick this up here
I've picked up so much already, I'm confused
Stop eating, just for a bit
This is strong
That's way too crazy
Crazy
Wait a sec, Chimera's appearing
What is this?
Hey, that hits!
One hit
This is crazy
It's coming
It's coming, crazy
Crazy
Sorry
Up there, super...
This, I mean...
If you pick up the stage, it's dangerous
Do your best
Bye-bye
Sorry, that's sad
Let's go
Ugh, wow
Won, won
Won
Run away
Here you go—oh!
Yeah
Ttaa~
Yatta~!
Bennett is tough.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Samus's charged attack is scary! Samus's charged attack...
It'd be nice if it were spacious.
The stage—yeah, definitely.
Stages are random anyway.
That's true too.
Matchups matter, yeah.
I also want to try out some characters...
...so I’ll give it a go!
What about Donkey Kong?
Donkey’s strong, I think—his down-B.
It’s super strong.
Down-B.
You know...
If you just keep spamming down-B, B, B, B, B, B—it’s really strong!
Oh, huh!
OK!
Let's go! Let's go! Oh!
It’s Joker!
Joker! Joker! I'm the Joker!
I'm the Joker, baby—ah!
Kirby actually seems strong.
When I thought Kirby was strong...
...it was crazy, seriously. Poyo!
Poyo poyo poyo—Mario!
Z has become Samus.
Z is B-button, B-button! Meme—OK!
B-button, full max charge!
No way, no way, no way!
Oh yes, yes, yes!
Gonna charge for a bit.
Nice missile!
And then Zizeta! Zizeta!
Golden Car! Golden balls! Golden balls!
Yay! *clap clap clap*
Okai-san!
You’re out! Huh?
Golden balls!
Okai said it!
And besides, Curry—
—there’s even a name like 'Golden Balls English'!
Golden Ball, everyone!
Even in Japanese, you kinda know it, right?
Golden Ball!
OK, Golden Ball!
I love Golden Ball!
OK, that got a laugh! It really did!
Good for you!
Worldwide Gold Ghost!
It’s over already.
Guess it really does get across—bye-bye!
Plus...
...it’s Door-sama’s frame, you know? Seriously!
Everyone uses other people’s frames...
Golden Ball!
Don’t say it so much!
Golden Ball—sorry!
Wait, this place...
...wasn’t this somewhere you shouldn’t get caught by your mom?
Ah, seriously—you really shouldn’t get caught here by your mom!
Yeah, yeah!
You really mustn’t get caught!
Oh!
Huh... ho...
—
Ah—
Boon!
Okae!
Okae’s strong! Okae’s strong!
Whoa—ah!
Whoa!
Strong! Ora! Congratulations!
So strong!
Alright! Recommended Samus! Recommended!
Yeah.
She’s strong, right?
Samus is definitely strong, but...
...probably...
...Senior Okae’s Samus...
...and my Samus are a little different.
That's not true at all.
One more, one more, one more
One more to go
Let's go!
Long time no see!
Fox is so narrow.
Donkey is huge!
It'd be bad if you fall!
Bye-bye!
What?
Stop!
Too strong!
This is strong!
Super scary!
Scary!
Bye-bye!
Zelda can jump too, so...
Might be strong, yeah.
Yeah, having long-range is really strong, isn't it?
Zelda's cute, huh?
Zero na—
Nice! Wait a sec...
Let's go with Donkey again.
Donkey might be good too.
Come on, Shiori!
Steve!
I'm Steve.
Steve, Steve, Sonic!
It's literally the curve that lets Steve ride the minecart!
Straight ahead!
Steve!
Geez!
This is tough!
Live 3's potato was a perfect game!
The map is crazy good—Steve!
Steve's minecart was amazing!
Steve's minecart is insane!
That curve is wild!
Gee Gee, come on!
Gee Gee, come on! Here it comes, here it comes!
It's coming!
Scary, scary!
Steve!
Hang in there, Steve!
Where's Shirtless Steve?
Huh?
Couldn't see it.
Like Donkey and...
Scary!
Oh no!
Wait, is that corpse Steve? That's bad!
Sorry, everyone—I couldn't get you in.
I'm sorry.
Just listen to my voice...
Sorry.
Please just imagine it from my voice.
Steve's insane!
Scary!
Dangerous!
Steve's scary!
Steve LT
TNT tr
o
Minecart jammed, Ste
ve! Steve, you're seriously great!
Steve!
Steve's scary!
Amazing!
Nice fight!
Wha—
—ba!
My palms are sweating like crazy from the one-on-one with Steve!
Oh no, oh no!
Gee Gee, Steve is seriously scary!
Nice fight!
Shoot!
Shoot, Steve!
Next, I'll use Sharpless Cephalos!
I'll use Sharpless! Sharpless!
Sharpless's shirt
Steve's shirt
Good idea
Wait, wait a sec
Sephiroth
Sephiroth's shirt—Sephiroth's shirt is insane!
The stream layout itself
Turns skin-colored? No way!
Setty... Sepharize
Yes
Another Sepharize
Another one
Using a sword, yes
Thanks! Let's go—this is insane!
Off-shot Sephiroth
Private Sephiroth
No
This is crazy!
Private time, okay
It's a summer vacation
Handsome guy vacation
Handsome guy
Springs Vacation, huh
Still alive
Still alive—alright!
Ah
Ah, Zero's vacation
Ah, Shiori Silver—whoa!
It's Jora!
Jora
Seriously, it's Silver
Seriously! It's Silver together!
Which one is Kan-chan's?
Ku-na Kan
Kan
This is a scene I've seen so many times
If he didn't have a shirt
He'd get even stronger
If he really had no shirt
You're joking—laughing
It's turning into a joke party
There's no character who can take off clothes either
Alright then, let's go with a character who can strip
A character who can undress
Off-shot character, off-shot character
Doesn't Link have any off-shots?
Link probably doesn't
No Link, huh
Like Donkey Kong
He's basically not even wearing anything already
True
Team Off-shot
Let's go
Curry, come on—Summer Vacation Curry, come on—that's right
Okay, I'm coming in! Okay, let's go!
Okay
Alright
Ah
Fulton’s here already!
I missed it again!
It's super thin
Looks like the three brothers now
Sorry
I still don't know who the detective is
I have to stay here, right?
While being here
I guess I have to touch this spot
Just for fun, okay?
Which character would be good?
Car! It's a car!
Ouch
Huh?
Is Link strong?
Gigi is House
The Geezer is House, Steve
Steve number one
Steve is crazy!
He's just really good at using Steve
Probably 'cause Gigi's skilled
It's the Mind Card
The Mind Card is strong
That's all there is to it
I really wanna do Geezer-is now
Geezer-is, come on!
Steve
That's brutal! 1v1!
1v1
One more person
OK
I'll kill Kaliopi even more! Kill, kill!
It's because I'm the Grim Reaper, right? This map...
This map is crazy! Crazy, seriously!
Here comes the minecart again—
Where do you want to go?
Crazy! Crazy!
Toa's riding it!
Toa was on the minecart!
She was just riding it...
Toa-chan!
Brutal!
This map, this map, Steve!
Too strong!
This place is insane! Wait, wait, wait!
I want to choose!
That's insane! Okay!
Oh!
You should have lived!
Wait up!
Geez's Steak
Gee Heating Child
Amazing!
Strong!
Way too strong! That's good!
Team vibe! Team vibe!
Seriously, seriously—team vibe fight!
We're on the same team, so do your best!
Yeah, that's right!
Same team! We did it together, same team!
Lock in Gee!
Me Too Last Game
Okay!
Well then,
Me Too Last—go for it!
Do your best!
Do your best! I'll do my best!
Teo Galgon's pink color
Sweet color!
Crazy!
Bullets are crazy! Why?!
Right!
Yuka! Yu-chan!
Scary! Scary!
Scary! Scary! Scary!
My house!
Ouch!
Pikachu is crazy!
Shiny Pikachu is strong, right?
Dangerous! Dangerous!
Dangerous! Nooo!
Is it coming from behind?
Because it's a boomerang!
Crown!
I see!
Because I learned the move!
Crazy! Can I dodge it?
Even with the crown, maybe I can just guard it, right?
I can't see the guard!
Absolutely!
Wow!
Alright, then—
With this, the white hair will fall! Good job! Thank you! Thank you!
Of
course, yeah
let's go
Go go
Huh? Zeta?
If you beat him, is it Steve?
No, it's not Steve
It's Sans now! Oh—
Simple is good!
Sans vs. Sephiroth
I'd love to see that!
Let's go!
Sephiroth looks strong if you unlock him!
Sephiroth!
Ah—I'll do it!
Don't do it!
Whoa!
Fireball!
Oh!
The old man's playing this game...
Someone's gonna smash it! LOL
Oh
Reiner
haha
She's hiding, haha
Laughing along
please
Do you prefer someone with a long reach?
Yeah
But I feel like Pikachu would be fine
Love Pikachu, love Pikachu
It's simple
and I think it feels really good
Come on
Okay, of course, forever
Good, good
Please go ahead, second person
And then, and then
and then
and then, and then
I've already said it twice lol
Sexy shirt vault hey hey hey gyowing
Kyaa
You gotta guard properly
Wheeeeeeeeee 444
Staff, just a sec
Jiji’s in trouble, just a sec
Just a sec—ah, just a sec, no, this is bad
Just a sec, whoa whoa whoa
Let’s talk about Zeta
Can you use Guard?
Awesome
Maybe you should guard
Guard is important, guard is important
Surely he’ll come
Surely time
You have to do it together with Zeta
You have to match me
Okay, okay
I need to match too
Come back here
Come back as an even cuter Pudding
Okay, okay
Okay, Pudding
Cute cute character vs Sephiroth
Sephiroth
That seems kinda weird
Maybe that’s not quite right
Pikachu, Pudding, Kabigon
Sephiroth
One cute team versus Sephiroth alone
Scary
Looks strong
What is this Pudding Pudding, that’s insane
Zigglebar
It’s definitely not Stiff yet
Stiff Mine Cart
Made of titanium
Tears, his mining power
Go check it out
Excitement
feeling
Who sold you the sharp from Sephrowatts?
No
Who sold you the sharp, sha
arp—who sold you the sharp?
This is bad
ba
d
Wait a sec
This is bad, ah
Huh?
What is it?
Damn
Going all-in with just one Thunderbolt
Strong, huh? Yeah, really strong
Fuu-san, should we do that thing?
Make it the last one, the very last one
OK, last one, last one
Alright, go ahead, Zeta, please
Do your best
Shiori, will you do it with Zeta and Jiji? Last one, go ahead
I think that’d be better
Let’s take a quick look
Last one
Do your best, Steve
Steve
Steve is totally giving it his all
Shuri, you do your best too
Steve is really strong
But what's important is
Aim for pitch-black Steve—it's dangerous
Wait a sec
Steve
Go!
Bye-bye
Steve, she's killing me
Oh no
That's bad
Zeto-chan, your hair fell out
This bookmark is super strong
Strong
So strong
Delicious, so delicious
That was fun—thank you
That was fun
Well then
Do your best for the real thing—practice hard
I'll practice lots and lots
Do your best—I believe in you! Leave it to me, leave it to me
Thank you
Thank you very much for watching today
Shiori's team is
Where are they?
Raora
I forgot—it's Team Bird, right? The bird team
Chicken! Chicken, okay
Team Chicken and Team Window, yes
Team Wind
Let's do our best
Let's do it
With that, great job everyone
Great job! Great job!
Great job
Alright, great job!
Great job! See you again—peace!