Hmm...
—Hmm—
O
pened it—
Yeees!
So then,
today, we'll be practicing as Team Bird, okay?
I'd like to do that.
No waaay~
First off,
let's start with quick self-introductions.
Starting from the top, please—Risu!
Should we start with the seniors?
Me first?—Hello!
Poro poro
Kanba Rissu
I'm Ayunda Risu,
from Hololive ID's Gen 3.
Nice to meet you all—
Nice to meet you—
Volume seems fine too.
I see.
I'd appreciate it if you could let me know.
Seems alright, I think?
Awa awa awa awa
OK OK! Next up, Kiara-senpai, please!
Kiki Ariki, Hololive English's Takane Kiara here!
I'm probably the only non-bird in this group.
That's true.
Yeah, definitely.
But since this is my first time playing this game,
I'm a total beginner—sorry about that!
Please take care of me—please take care of me!
Please take care of me!
Looks good.
Next, Pekora—hope that's okay?
I came over from Team Wind as a skater!
That's Pekora—Peko, Pekora also
kinda, um, mixed it up with another game
and confused it with a different one
There are similar ones, right? Yeah, yeah!
I thought it was that one
and now I'm like, 'Oh no, oh no!'
But Risu-chan and Kiara-chan,
and Suu-chan are here,
so we'll definitely be fine!
Let's absolutely win!
Let's all win together!
Nice to meet you all!
Spish—I'm Suu Minato!
Suu's also a complete beginner,
so today I want to try my best
while learning lots from Senpai Risu!
Nice to meet you all—!
Nice to meet you—!
Yoshi yoshi yoshi
Preparations—Ah, never mind, gather here!
Ah, right here!
Okay!
Let's give it a try first.
Let's just try it out and see how it goes.
So first,
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Since everyone's suited for different roles, I'm sure
Alright!
What's this?
Let's ask Risu-chan for help with everything.
There are couples here and there, but
Huh? What does that mean?
What even are these couples?
Couples are, umm…
Customers?
Ah, customers!
Yeah, couples mean two people
coming together as a pair, right?
I get it now.
Okay!
Got it!
So, umm…
Is this the prep area?
Prep
What are they even doing?
Preparation
Easy movement patterns
meaning we should arrange things for easier movement, right?
How should we go about that?
Risu-chan, where should
we position ourselves to make it easier?
What makes it easier...
How about a burger, then?
Maybe here?
This place is fine.
With this, okay?
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Hey, Pekora, why...
Why isn't this human?
Do you understand?
Someone, why is this happening?
Why did Pekora turn into this machine?
Pekora, why don't you get it?
Why can't you just be human, no matter what?
What is this thing?
I could choose my favorite.
That...
I didn't choose it! I didn't choose it!
Seriously, I didn't pick anything—what is this? What is this?
Skates are shaped like this, apparently.
What's going on?
I don't know either.
Supposedly, if you hold the button down, it turns into a crane.
I held the button down for a bit.
I didn't press anything!
I wonder what's going on.
Once we start, we might not be able to go back.
No, we'll go back.
I'm pretty sure we'll go back, right?
Probably gonna be fine.
This is super fun—only one person!
Ah, it went back! It went back!
I was just riding it.
Huh?
How did it go back?
Hobby!
Use the controller.
Ah, it went back! It went back!
Thank you, thank you!
First, who's going to be who?
We should decide our roles beforehand.
Um...
I don't want to do the burger!
I really don't want to do the burger!
That selfishness won't fly, Kiyotaka!
You just have to do the burger!
Follow me, secretary!
Follow me—even as a secretary, you gotta do it!
Very well! Yes, I'm listening, I'm listening!
Hello!
Good, good, good—okay, okay!
Okay, okay, okay!
It's cramped in here.
This place might be super cramped.
Looks tight anyway, huh?
You know...
Order!
So fast!
Taking orders!
Yes!
Are you okay?
Trash is appearing—no trash should be made!
Rename Restaurant!
Why is someone standing outside alone?
Risu-chan!
This person...
Aren't they waiting?
Waiting!
Waiting! Waiting line!
I see.
It's already turning into chaos!
It's already turning into sara hara suke!
Tr
ash is being created!
Trash is being created!
This place is insane!
This place is insane! This place is insane!
Sorry!
Sorry like this!
The idiots are finally showing their stupidity!
Oh no!
The patty's in trouble!
I'm not even handling the patty!
Why is this happening?
People are waiting so much!
It's crazy—too popular, it's insane!
Game!
It might have changed!
This is the 4000th time!
First...
Got it on the first try, right? It's narrow here.
It's narrow, narrow here, so maybe this spot?
Yes, yes, yes!
Let's go with that side.
Yes, let's do that.
Yes, let's do that. Let's put it here.
This spot is made for two people to fit, you know. It fits.
Do we really need to wash things like bread too?
If we don't wash them, we won't be able to call many people.
I see.
This comes off.
If it's around here, Suu and Kiara-senpai can come to wash stuff, so closer might be better.
Closer.
Where exactly?
This spot is fine.
Probably.
They should be able to come wash things.
Who's in charge of burgers?
If it's about making burgers, I might be okay.
Just one person.
Risu-chan handles burgers.
And washing...
Washing dishes.
Pecora will wash them. OK.
Taking orders, delivering food, and cleaning.
Let's all work together!
This might actually work.
Alright!
Perfect?
Where do they bring the dishes, I wonder?
They'll bring them here.
Here.
Right here.
The dirty ones.
Huh?
Puno's here.
So fast!
Way too fast!
Dishes!
Yes, yes, yes!
OK, OK.
Already put them down.
Still no dishes yet.
OK, OK.
That's fine!
Risu-chan as cook is perfect!
No...
Wait a sec—this is undercooked!
There's even undercooked stuff. Thanks!
Wash this! Wash this one!
Can't put it here—over here!
Which one do I wash?
Which one needs washing?
I'll put it here. Right here.
Thank you!
Ah, oh no—the burger!
Bur-
-ger! I'll take it!
Order key! Order key! Oh no!
Order key incoming!
Washing, washing—burger #1!
Tsukuda-san! Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Washing, washing!
Huh?
Um...
One order didn't make it in time.
Huh? Wait, it just got busy, right?
Huh?
This is bad!
This is tough.
Hold on a second!
Washing dishes is hard!
Should we stay closer?
Actually, here...
Coming all the way here to wash stuff...
Should dishwashing be done here?
Hmm...
Saraare, not there!
Um...
We can do it from here.
So it can be done from there!
Yeah, that's really good!
Maybe this spot?
If even one person escapes, it's an instant game over.
This is tricky!
This is seriously bad!
Plus...
Saraare is surprisingly tough too.
It was pretty tough, huh... Hmm.
Scarier than I thought!
Trash is also coming out onto the floor, so
I tried to clean the floor trash first, but
Maybe the waiters should handle it.
That's true.
Then, when Pekora has free hands,
Pekora will go.
OK OK OK, I'm already here.
There's no place to put it.
Can I put it there?
No, no, can't put it there—it's bad!
If you put it over here, then over there...
Bringing burgers~!
This is already bad.
Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad!
When Risu-chan is cooking
and helping wash Pekolan's dishes,
Wait, what's going on?
Risu,
You're way too strong.
There are burgers!
There are burgers! Be careful!
Yeah.
Plates!
No plates! Here, plates—here!
Yes, yes, yes!
Is anyone around right now?
It's fine.
The store's running smoothly.
Alright~
It's running well, yeah.
Ah, forever and ever and ever
Cleaning, cleaning—ah, this is bad!
This person—ahhhhhh!
What are you doing?
Higher—eh, what was that?
The level just finished was way too high.
I probably don't get it.
Don't get it, don't get it.
The level was just so incredibly high.
Why though?
Why did we just die?
Again!
We couldn't keep up with the orders.
It was too fast, right?
That couple...
Something...
One of them...
Right when one raised their hand,
it felt like things suddenly sped up.
I wonder what's going on.
Maybe we should've waited until both were ready before serving.
Can't we get more plates?
This...
Aren't there too few plates?
The number of plates is really low, isn't it?
It's too few, right?
Wait, hold on.
Risu-chan, please take a look.
Any points for improvement?
Did you have any advice or suggestions?
Like, maybe
'You should do it like this here,'
or something like that?
Washing the plates—the plates...
From here, it's somehow barely
manageable.
Starting from here, from here...
Let's just do it here, then.
It's doable from here.
While also doing that?
Is it okay if I move it a bit?
It's kind of far, but would it get in the way?
Well, anyway...
It's in the way.
Would it be in the way?
We can do it.
Let's try doing it closer.
This spot is in the way.
It was too far and we couldn't make it in time.
Let's make this into a large two-person table.
This and this will be big
two-person tables. I see.
Just two people is enough?
Customers basically only come in pairs.
But sometimes groups of four show up.
Group sizes are mostly 1 or 2 people.
But this is too far away,
and we couldn't keep up multiple times earlier,
so we don't need it over there, right?
But
I feel like it was good just now
I think this part is totally fine
Easy to serve
Like, Kiara-san, I guess
When a couple comes
If you give the dish to just one of them
Probably
The other person will finish way too quickly
It might be better to serve them both at the same time
Oh, really?
Like, simultaneous serving, yeah, that's super
It got finished so fast
Simultaneous is probably better
Then
Give it to both people at once—ho, ho, ho
Alright
Let’s try it again once more—haaai!
Pekora will try even harder
Do your best!
First, here
So I don't get in Disu-chan's way
Such an intense review meeting
I need to respond, but
What’s going on?
Yes
Two orders came in
It’s fine since they’re not a couple
Are you sure?
Why is the button response so slow?
Maybe someone threw the controller or something
And it broke
There’s definitely a chance
That might actually be the case from here on
The burger finishes cooking before the plate arrives
I seriously want that
Don’t act like you don’t know
This is bad
Go go go go, good good good—hmm
Yes yes yes yes, hello
Here—one each
This
Can’t wash the plates?
Ah, ah—this is the hot plate button
Why can’t this be washed?
Punishment
It’s washing
Plate washing is kinda slow
It’s slow, right?
Plate washing, plate washing—it’s slow, right?
You guys should start from the back there
Should do it from the free spot in the back
Plate washing is tough
They said if someone’s already using it, you can’t wash
Plate washer, hang in there, just a bit
Hand-washing—why, why is this so stupid?
One more, please
No no no—one more program, please
Seriously, one more program—hey, this
“Can’t wash”—what’s wrong with this thing?
This, Sara’s washing
Might need to switch once
Try it, Jio-san
Kiara will try
Kiara-chan, give it a try
She’ll definitely end up staying overnight like Pekora, seriously
Really?
It’s not just that Senpai Pekora is bad at it
It’s that the buttons don’t work well
I don’t think it’s Pekora’s fault
Maybe the response is just hard to trigger
Do I just carry the plates?
Yes, yes
OK OK
Just one game
They’re underestimating this
Orders
Yes yes yes yes, two came in
Two are ready
Send it over, Senpai Pekora
This one, Senpai Pekora
Huh?
Eh, what?
Something...
There's someone not working...
No
I am! I am working!
Huh, wait—maybe Pekora's lagging?
Maybe it's lagging
Might be lagging
Wha—
My stomach's getting grabbed
People are getting exhausted
Wait, hold on
Senpai Pekora, please work
Pekora-senpai said she's working, right?
I'm doing it already!
I didn't come here as a spy
Hey, this
Wait, crap—this is lagging
Lag
No, that
I actually washed it normally
Kiara, that's wrong—it's lagging, lagging!
This thing from Japan is seriously lagging
I've been completely defeated
Indonesia's actually closer to Japan, and
Probably
Kiara might have the worst lag
Everyone doesn't know this, right?
It might be lagging—this is bad
I can't place it, and furthermore, why
Why
What are you doing?
Seriously, seriously, no—I really mean it
This isn't spying
There really is a spy
Seriously, seriously, seriously
It's just one person operating, but
Hold on
I couldn't place it—but I did, I placed it
Suddenly Anime
Amazing
Wait a sec—this is seriously serious
No, no—hey, be careful, don't joke around
Seriously, please help me out
Pekora won't do anything about this
I'll wash it properly
Heave-ho
Seriously, seriously—this is weird
This
It's not like Pekora's doing that
Look, look—everyone's movements
Are weird, see?
I was acting a bit strange too
It rewound
Look
Pekora
It happened, it happened
This is bad—super funny
Pekora-senpai can't do anything
Do your best!
Funny, it's alright
Sometimes things just go like this, right?
Yeah, sometimes it happens
Yosa-sakashi-iru oi sararan yan
The inside guy—oi sararan
You said 'sararan' earlier, right?
Senpai really should work—look
Senpai, look
Work already, come on
Well, sometimes you just get tired
What's this now?
Dangerous, dangerous—so dangerous!
This role
We actually managed it perfectly with the switch, didn't we?
Did it, did it
Yes, Kami
Kami, even beating the lag
This could work
By the way, seriously
Mizumi was solo-operating
Pekoro-senpai, no—that's not it, so
I was solo-operating
It was a bit laggy
Movements were bad
Even Pekoro with this
But still, we cleared it
True
What are we supposed to earn after clearing it?
What are we making into a team competition?
This thing...
How exactly do we compete?
In the end, what exactly are we supposed to do here?
Is there some kind of score that makes us better than the other teams?
This thing...
Speed or something?
Speed.
Uh, I wonder... probably speed?
It's probably speed, for now anyway.
Ah, like Day 2 or something like that.
What awareness are we trying to create?
Number of days.
Yeah.
It says 'number of days'—ah, so it's about days.
We need more tables.
Ah, so that means we can get more customers.
Should we give it a try?
That could work—if it's based on days,
then prep time counts too, right?
But maybe it doesn't matter.
Since it's not about speed.
I wonder if we can take as much prep time as we want.
That's true.
If it's only about days,
can we even add more sinks?
But we don't have any money though.
Money.
Did we just spend all our money on tables?
Yeah.
Since Re-chan is already at the table,
maybe Mario can handle it?
Let me say it again.
As long as we work hard, it'll be fine.
There won't be any lag next time.
Leave it to me.
Do your best.
Because we're seriously going for the win.
Pekora's serious today, okay?
Even though she told us, 'Let's win!'
Pekora-senpai's acting weird too.
This is A, right? Yeah, it's A.
Right? See, it's A.
It's working, it's working!
It's working—go ahead, go ahead!
It's working right now.
With this,
we'll serve it as A.
See?
We're working, you know!
Work!
Sara-san,
you might not actually make it—you're surprisingly slow.
I'll deliver it! Right when it lights up!
Probably.
Like this.
X.
X?
Made it! You got it! We did it!
Yes, thank you very much!
It feels better than last time.
Smoothly.
Now! Now!
Ah, lagging, lagging, lagging—stop it!
Oh no!
Plates, plates, plates—might be in trouble, plates!
Might be in trouble.
Oh no, oh no, might be in trouble!
The plates...
Man, I really need another sink...
Hey, dish person!
What are you doing, Dish Person-chan?
Let's do this properly!
Huh? Pekora-senpai?
Didn't it take like 10 seconds just to get to the back?
Well, uh, Pekora-senpai was...
when you were doing the dishes,
you were working the whole time, right?
By the way,
No, no, Pekora-san,
Risu-chan-san,
Could you call her again?
Pekora-san might be super laggy.
Maybe I should restart this.
Yeah, I'll restart it. In advance...
If someone else is already making a room...
I'm not sure what'll happen to my level...
I don't know what'll happen if I try it.
Is it okay if I make a room?
Didn't they say there's a minimum level requirement?
I still think it's fine to make a room now.
Anything's fine, Rishan.
Could you call Pekora for me?
Because she'll be coming back.
Okay, I'll try calling Senior Pekora again.
Thank you.
But if the lag gets really bad...
Maybe someone else should create the room next time.
There's probably something like a level...
Only Senior Risu can probably open a Kampoofer room.
So it's only Senior Risu...
That's why...
Today, while leveling up...
Let's level up.
Tonight...
Let's make it so anyone can create a room.
Here comes Pekora—the hardest worker of them all!
She's here!
Let's go! Am I mistaken?
My memory...
Let's go, let's go!
Let's start!
Let's start! Work, work!
Yes, yes, yes!
Let's go!
It feels a bit better now.
Does Suu-chan's thing actually work?
It kind of...
It works!
It works! Does this menu item actually work?
Okay, okay.
Then, Bekoro...
This one person...
It works! Yes!
Yes, hellooo!
I heard it.
I didn't hear it.
Please press the up button to hear it.
I heard it, I heard it!
Great, great!
Just a moment, please.
Let's influence things here.
The two of us...
Ready—go!
Right here—the up button...
I don't really get it, but...
I heard it!
You're doing a great job washing dishes—very nervously!
Speak up, come on!
Everyone, if you don't lend your wages...
We'll lose to the other teams!
Amazing!
Suddenly, energetic Senior Pekora...
I'll provide it to each of you individually.
Yes.
Provided to one person.
Thank you very much!
We're short two burgers.
Plates, please!
Then, these two...
Let's do it together!
But we're not a couple, so...
It's fine if you go ahead first.
Ah, okay!
Yes, OK OK OK OK—I'll bring it!
I'll bring it!
Yes, yes, here you go!
Here you are!
An order is coming in!
Thank you for your order!
How exactly are they hearing this...
I seriously don't get it.
Oh no!
This place is super dirty!
Seriously, it's gross!
Let's properly clean the floor.
I'll clean up.
Leave after you eat, hurry up and leave, customers too, quickly
Customers, leave too—don't stay forever!
There
Because we're a couple
We have to do two things
First, first, this side is fine
Down, let's go down first, OK OK OK
Leave after eating
Leave quickly after eating
Heave-ho, heave-ho
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho
Hey, wait—I just finished
It's starting to look good—oh yeah!
This is the real deal—exaggeration works, it works!
Pecorasseppa, this one
Let's bring it together
Akeke—oh no, oh no, okay
Isn't it perfect? Amazing, beautiful!
It was hard to work, but it feels good now
Hey, can we buy plates?
What are we buying?
Can we buy plates?
There's a pen on the envelope
Plate rack
There are plates
20 coins, 20 coins
We can buy sinks too, and plates
Both are good
Good, the sink is right here
What's a reservation desk?
Reservations are probably by phone
Phone
Don't we need a phone? No way
It's tough, after all
Day 3
We can do it anytime, really
We have extra money, so maybe we should buy something
Using an Xbox controller
Bought pink
Maybe I'll buy plates too
If I put this sink by this door
Maybe everyone can barely fit stuff here too
Indeed, from here
OK
Might work
It's responding—good, it works, it works!
Seems doable
Nice
Helpful! Nice, nice, nice
Let's give it a try
Let's go, let's go
The tasks won't change, right?
Yes
One customer has arrived—please come in!
Ah, it's two people
Two people
These guys surprised me
I thought it was just one person
Alright
Ah, sorry, sorry, ah
Is the trash bin far?
Hey, maybe we can move the trash bin closer—it's crazy
Ah, crap! Ah, we won't make it in time—crazy!
Ah, sorry—it's fine, even pros mess up
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
It happens sometimes
I served it a bit too early
The chef must be under a lot of pressure
You can't afford to fail
Chef
Thank you
Alright, let's go
Let's go
Yes
Welcome!
Plates!
Welcome, welcome—delicious!
Alright
Yes, okay, here they come, here they come, here they come
Yes, okay, it's come. Yes, go ahead.
Thank you very much.
Yeah, Zuwan, once you eat, you gotta go home.
Once you eat, you gotta go home.
Yes, one order of hamburger for one person.
One piece, right.
Don't mess up the route.
Don't mess up the route, okay.
Yes, this guy, okay.
Well then...
I'll take one hamburger.
Alright, alright.
Yes, once you eat, go home.
Once you eat, go home, you're heading back already.
Once you eat, go home.
Yes, Zu...
Wan.
Thanks a lot!
Okay, then I'll serve it now.
Serving.
Thank you very much.
Well then...
Moving on to the menu.
I'll serve it.
Nice!
A nice couple just arrived.
Ra...
Okay.
Washing dishes.
Just for a moment...
I'll leave this here for now.
So...
Senior couple, taking your order now.
Yes, going now.
Yes, okay.
Alright, I'm going now.
Okay.
Nice! Another couple again.
Ca...
-uple is super popular.
Couples love it.
Yeah.
Miss Woman's...
Heave-ho, heave-ho.
Alright, with this, let's go to the lower couple. Okay.
Entering the active phase.
Yes, while handling the fifth customer, nice job.
Nice! Five people quickly.
Alright!
Shift will end soon.
Alright, OK.
Ah, OK—plates!
Wash the plates properly like this, okay.
Please order only what you can finish.
Last order—one item only.
Yes, please go ahead. Okay.
Then, to Su-chan...
Was still entering it.
Right now, two more orders came in.
There's an order there.
I'm not really sure how to take orders—the bar's ready!
Bringing it now! Bringing it to the back!
Yes, here you go.
The bar's ready!
Feeling good, feeling good.
You'll get spoiled!
Clean it up~
Perfect! Amazing!
Not bad!
This place is the best! The absolute best!
Awesome! Great job! Oh, stars!
It's getting good reviews.
Reputation improved, timing got better.
No, that's great.
Working is fun, isn't it?
This, you see...
What's this?
We shouldn't add things like cherry pie, right?
Just burgers, right?
Exactly, exactly.
Well then...
We have no choice but to increase staff.
What do you mean by increasing staff?
More customers objectively means more guests.
This...
How do you write a letter...
Dining...
Sink, sink, work boots.
Work
Easily open the shoe door
Move easily through crowds
Honda
Spreads dirt
Honda dirt
It ends up spreading the dirt, huh
That's probably not great
Add something?
The sink—here, sorry, Pekora
It's kind of hard to wash
I left dishes here
I briefly thought maybe Kiara was finding it a bit difficult
How about it?
Seems okay
Sometimes I leave dishes out
It was fine
Leaving them is totally fine
This side might be okay
You should be able to place things from outside too, just in case
But maybe it's a bit tight
This corner
Even from this angle
This door goes through, so you can place things through it
Okay, okay
Just go back like that—it'll make me laugh
Okay
Shouldn't we change something?
There's some lag
Uh, hey, hey
Laggy
Ugh
Wait, Pecoro's running super smoothly right now
Actually,
Ah, it just became smooth
Fixed!
Okay
Ah, we can recreate Blue Prince now
Even in this upgrade test
One more round
Should we keep it like this?
Yeah, let's try one round
Wait a sec
What's up?
Wait a moment, everyone
Ah, it's Suichan
The teacher came
The teacher came! The teacher!
Sorry
Just a sec
I finished my errand
Welcome back!
A guest arrived!
The teacher came to help us
A pro came! A pro came!
We’re on a bit of a time limit
I have plans right after this, so...
I see
Is there someone who knows the details?
Plate up
No one? Maybe only Risu-san?
Only Senpai Risu—Risu knows best
Risu
Right now, with the hamburger
Together with the hamburger
So you've already started?
We've started
Yeah, yeah, yeah—that thing
Ah
We need to upgrade stuff like the dishwasher
Dishwasher
What's that?
Seriously?
Can we actually use upgraded versions?
We wash by hand at our place
You don't even wash by hand yourself
Do you understand the rules for this round?
Time, time
Huh?
I don't get it—time attack?
Time attack
The rule this time is time attack, right?
P-probably
I don't know, honestly
Wait, wait, wait!
Yeah, yeah, hold on a sec!
I'll go check real quick!
What's 'Time Attack'?
Does it mean finishing the day as quickly as possible?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Next, I'll set it right here.
Okay!
These are couples, right?
Two people as a couple, okay?
That was great, seriously!
If Suichan hadn't come...
Pekora and the others...
...would've been playing without understanding any of the rules.
Hey, listen...
While watching the stream...
I was wondering if you'd be alright...
But you were totally fine, weren't you?
It actually went pretty well!
But hey, your gameplay was super shaky!
Pekora!
Senpai, let's go as a couple!
Let's do it!
Couple!
Plate up!
Oh no!
The customers are already shouting 'Rules! Rules!'
Right now, if we could just serve one more plate...
Then this capo would go 'capo!'
Capo!
Nice!
Huh? Wait, so...
Slither Senpai, is it only for one day?
Ah, no, no, no, no!
Um, there's a time limit...
A 15-minute time limit, yes, yes, yes!
You earn 50 points multiplied by the number of stages cleared within 15 minutes.
So basically, you need to rush through as many stages as possible in those 15 minutes. For example...
If you reach Day 5...
That's 250 points!
Exactly!
So things like...
...the time spent selecting items need to be done super fast.
This too, huh?
Is John Bee's Time Mode also like that?
I see, got it!
Right, and also...
I think the map is predetermined.
Map?
What's a map?
Is the map not fixed?
Well, um...
It is fixed—the seed value is set.
Right now...
There are lots of rooms down in the bottom-left corner, right?
This shape of the store...
This time, we won't use that area.
Um, the top floor plan...
You know this one, right?
Next to it, there's a place where you can set the seed value...
Enter the seed value 'CUDDLE'.
Then...
Could someone type 'CUDDLE' into the chat, please?
Then, somehow...
It should turn into the Hero Show room, I think!
Would this side be easier to handle?
Probably, yeah.
This time, we'll use that setup, plus City...
Not the right one—wait, the top-left one!
City mode...
And with those rules...
Making burgers...
...and seeing how quickly you can complete it within 15 minutes!
Blade Up gives you various items, right?
All sorts of...
By evolving these items...
...you can work more efficiently.
Evolve!
Currently, dishwashing...
...is done by hand, but it can become a dishwasher!
Like being able to wash four at once.
How do you perform divine evolution?
How do you wash it?
You can only evolve once.
If you clear on day one,
you’re guaranteed to get an upgrade desk,
and it will drop.
There used to be something like an upgrade desk.
You buy that upgrade desk,
and there was something like a bookshelf, right?
It’s guaranteed to be green,
and there’s a bookshelf available from the start,
so you can place it there without buying it.
It dropped from that whistle,
that square item,
so you place it there without buying it.
Then start,
and after you’ve started,
keep smacking that upgrade desk repeatedly.
When the gauge maxes out,
it evolves.
Maybe you should try it once.
Unless you’ve started the game,
you won’t be able to upgrade it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
By the way, if you don’t mind,
could someone share their screen?
Please.
Thanks, that makes things easier.
I mean, it’s so huge,
isn’t that kind of crazy?
This one should be okay.
This.
I know how cramped it was before.
Given that,
does that make it easier to work with?
This.
I liked the cramped setup too.
I just shared my screen.
Thanks.
Well, but here,
what’s with all this space?
They arranged it so Ris-chan can move more easily.
Huff, huff.
Hah.
But there’s another trick,
Yeah, just now,
you know the letter has arrived, right?
And to go get that letter,
you step out of the door,
and you have to actually go over there.
I believe on the controller,
everyone is using controllers,
or Beer-chan on the keyboard,
hold B down,
and something like a crane appears.
Then,
you can slip through that wall.
By doing that,
you can set things up a bit quicker.
That’s why this exists.
Exactly, exactly.
Now, down below, there’s something green, right?
Is this the bookshelf-like thing?
This.
Yes, yes, the document shelf, that’s it.
Put the letter in there,
and place the upgrade desk right beside it,
and once it starts, go ahead and smack it repeatedly.
It won’t show up until you’ve cleared the Reiwa stage once.
I think it’s better to clear it first.
Plus,
since the map is large, the customers take longer to leave,
because the time it takes for customers to leave is wasted.
So, near the entrance, that table,
collecting dining tables might be an option too.
Ah, I see.
Yeah.
There are various options available around there.
Options like that.
Behind here, then,
it’s better if no one is present.
Guests take quite a while to leave, so you should head home early.
Go home.
So you mean placing it closer as part of our strategy?
Yeah, that's totally acceptable now.
That's great, Master!
It was dangerous—they almost didn't make it in time.
It really was dangerous; I'm truly satisfied now.
We can do this.
Actually, I've become even more anxious about various things...
Thanks to the area manager coming, I feel a bit better now.
We can do it.
Since we can practice from here on, we'll be fine.
Yeah, yeah, we can do it, we can do it!
If we have the knowledge,
we can apply it—okay!
Okay!
I'll do my best!
Alright, let's give it a try once.
For now, I'll
keep handling cleaning and plates and such.
Ah, the burger station is too far away.
Wait a sec—oh, right!
Ah, be careful! Yes, exactly, that's right!
Let's also find an easier way to make this.
Yes.
Where should we put it?
Nice, nice!
Great!
There are two spots by the window as well,
so if possible, let's place the burger station at just one of them
and clean only one spot
or place the plates there.
Unless there's no space, though...
Let's make this side the dirty one.
This side, closer to the sink.
Yes.
Let's go with that. And over here,
the cooking side of the mixer
could serve as the burger plating station.
Wouldn't this side be better?
I think that's good.
Alright, let's do it!
Let's go!
Hey-yo!
Two customers have arrived.
A couple, a couple!
Hi!
Alice-chan!
They might not actually be a couple...
They're definitely not a couple.
I couldn't hear that.
Ah, I heard it! I heard it!
Okay, okay, okay!
Gok-gok, gok, gok-gok!
Thanks for coming all the way in the rain!
These guys are standing way too close together,
making it kinda hard to pass through.
Thanks for this!
No problem!
While cleaning here, day one...
Isn't this way too relaxed?
Can you hear me?
At first, Pecorine and the others were in big trouble, though.
Day one wasn't nearly as smooth back then.
So there was a time like that, huh?
Yep, yep!
It just means we've gotten better.
Now we're pros, after all—exactly, exactly!
Aren't these guys making way too much of a mess?
100%!
I'll place the plates.
Thank you very much.
And...
Yes.
Yes, served successfully—nice job!
Risu-chan's
silent burger-making
is way too fast—unbelievably fast!
Isn't that seriously amazing?
Seriously, super fast!
That's incredible!
At this rate, they're definitely not a couple.
Burgers keep coming out nonstop!
Alrighty!
Yes
Yup, okay!
The speed
Yo-yoisho
I'll take your order
I'll place the order
Thank you very much
For now
Day 1 is fine, no worries, okay
Letters have started falling down
As expected, I opened all the letters that came down
Opened them by pressing hard on the bottle neck
And then
That sink and
That upgraded desk and
I really want to buy the upgraded desk first
But I don't have enough money to buy it
So I can't buy this on Day 1
Or maybe I can buy it, but
It's because of that issue with the customers
Sui-chan, what's going on here?
I think we should be able to buy it
But why can't we buy it right now?
Right now, I
Haven't bought the phone yet, right?
The very first phone
We ignored it, didn't we? We ignored it
Ah
We should buy it
We should get the phone
Yeah, buy the phone
Then, ring the phone—'chirin chirin chirin chirin'
When you ring it
Customers will suddenly come pouring in
Oh, really?
And each time you ring 'chirin,' it's like 9 yen, I think
If I remember correctly
That's how it comes in
You actually get quite a bit
Every time you ring it, so you should definitely buy that
Ring 'chirin chirin'
Call customers quickly and serve them right away
Then
You'll probably get around
50 yen on Day 1
Buying the phone first is a definite must
Yeah, thanks Sui-chan
This upgraded desk
If I want to buy it next
Probably
If you miss it here
It won't appear again
So put it in this filing cabinet
You can keep it saved, right? Yeah
You can carry it over to the next day
So you can take it out the next day and buy it
I think it's good to keep that in mind
Also
Since we didn't reduce chairs earlier
Customers were getting all mixed up
But you can actually remove chairs
This one
Just tap-tap it
Press X or something
X
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Wow, really—like this
Right
This thing
For example, near the entrance
There's a lot of customer traffic
So maybe move the chairs away from there
Right now, this corner seat
Might be a bit hard for customers to access
Because there's a chair in the corner
The bottom-right one, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
So maybe move this one like this?
Thinking about seat arrangements like this
Makes it even more fun
Thank you, Area Manager
Amazing
Please do take this advice into consideration
Anyway, since we don't have that phone yet
I guess we just have to go ahead and do it anyway
OK, OK, maybe it would've been better if we'd gotten a call.
Will we start taking reservations from day one?
Risu-chan said it's really tough.
Probably, Risu-chan, who's making it, is definitely...
Definitely seems inexperienced.
Because she's doing it all alone, you know.
I wonder if it'll be alright.
Then, there's a chance...
Kiara-chan, who's among them,
might help out a bit,
But is that okay?
If there's a chance it works out,
Like this...
Alright! I'll go ahead and take your order then—yes!
I can't take the order yet—I got it!
Yes, the order.
Yes.
I’ll just adapt to it.
It’s starting to feel good.
So fast, so fast!
Efficiency, efficiency!
It’s only day two, after all.
True, we only have 15 minutes, huh?
I wonder roughly how much we can get done.
This is actually amazing.
Should we ask the coder to listen in?
Co-
Have the coder listen in...
That’s pretty great!
Fast, fast—have the coder listen!
Here you go.
Whoa, awesome!
Clear!
We did it!
I see.
Well then...
We have 75 yen. What can we buy with that?
I wonder if that thing will appear. What will show up?
Will this become usable?
Yeah, we can buy that Multi-Pla.
Sink, yeah.
And then, put it beside...
Put the sink inside.
Inside the document shelf.
Put this green one inside here.
Yeah, exactly.
Like this...
Like this, maybe?
But...
The 'Plus' is showing up, right?
When 'Plus' appears and it starts, you can...
Hit it repeatedly...
to raise the gauge, right?
Although you can't do it until it actually starts.
I think we could buy other things too, if there's anything else we want.
This 'Multi Brush' thing is actually quite recommended.
Multi Brush.
This one?
Yeah, this one costs 20 yen.
It says dishwashing speed becomes three times faster.
That’s seriously awesome!
If you have this,
floor-cleaning speed also becomes super fast,
so it's recommended the dishwashing person keeps hold of it.
Outside, maybe?
Apparently it's best for the dishwashing person to keep it.
Or maybe inside is fine too?
Would Kiara be okay with it?
OK.
Also, about Kiara—I see.
Kiara should, right at the start when it begins,
upgrade this first...
Desk.
It might be better to tap it rapidly.
Right here—the digital one, yeah.
OK, OK, OK, good.
I’ll take it.
By the way, Kiara...
This document shelf...
can we rotate it to face forward?
Isn't it facing forward right now?
In this state,
it's hard to tell what it evolved into.
Let's spin it once more.
The green one...
Yeah, the green one—the green one! Like this...
Then you'll see what it evolves into, right?
Kind of, yeah.
Shall we try it like this?
If there's any part that's hard to use...
Maybe we should rearrange the layout.
The other side was totally fine, though.
Alright, let's give it another go.
Wow, how beautiful! Amazing, fantastic!
I wonder what it turned into?
A dishwasher! It became a dishwasher!
That's wonderful!
So does that mean we can use it from now on?
Yeah, exactly—it'll change next time.
This...
If we have this multi-brush...
Can we do anything else with it?
We can, we can!
Go ahead and try it.
It's super fast, right? So fast!
It's too fast—I'm confused!
Way too fast—now I'm bored!
Even when the dishwasher was ready...
Do we still need to use the mayo brush?
The dishwasher...
automatically washes the dishes, you know.
Hmm...
Well, maybe just try using it once...
It might be better to see for yourself how it works.
I think so too.
But honestly, washing them yourself is still faster.
So, if we're thinking about speedrunning (RTA)...
If you have that multi-brush...
Buy a slightly bigger sink...
And wash everything all at once there.
That’s probably the most efficient way, I think.
Oh no—it froze!
Something...
Feels laggy, doesn't it? Like it's puffing up.
Are you okay?
It was lagging for a bit, but it's fine now.
Okay, I see.
Alright, we'll buy the dishwasher but won't actually use it.
We can evolve the job diary again, right?
Then it’ll become a different sink again.
This...
It's random, right?
Is it random evolution?
Yes.
I think there are three possible evolutions for sinks.
There are three types?!
Wow!
Or maybe even four?
Well, if that's provided, then that's the end of it.
Here you go!
Ah, so fast, so fast!
Nice, nice!
It ended before I even noticed!
Clap clap, clap!
Clap clap!
This...
How many days' worth can we earn within 15 minutes?
Yeah, yeah.
Ah...
What should we do with the right side here?
Well, this one...
I'll leave it up to you.
It's only once per day anyway.
The left side gets more complicated with burgers, right?
Yeah, that's true.
More varieties get added.
We don't need that. I see.
There's a plate here.
What should we do?
I think it's better to buy it around now.
I see.
From here on, customers will increase dramatically...
And you'll start falling behind, you know.
Because of the number of plates.
Ah, I get it.
If three seats get filled by customers at once...
Right now, we only have four plates...
So if six people show up, we'll definitely run out of plates—that makes sense.
I kind of feel like maybe I should just go ahead and buy it.
I bought it.
Hmm?
So, are we ultimately not buying a dishwasher?
I'll leave it up to everyone—whether to buy one or
do something else instead. Where's this
this? Ah, I don't have any money.
But I can still manage fine with hand-washing for now.
Then, this
should probably stay hidden for now.
Isn't the dish placement too far away?
What about Carela?
I wonder what they'd think.
Well, I’ll always be passing through here anyway.
This is totally in the way.
In the way.
No, no, it's fine.
Okay.
Looks good.
Looks good. Everything's ready, so
next, let's replace the dishwasher. Okay.
Feels like it's running nicely.
Probably won't do the 'peshi-peshi' thing.
If you try it,
go ahead, give it a try!
I wonder what it'll turn into.
It'll be a Big Sink.
I'll leave it to your order.
Ah, not a Big Sink after all.
Maybe it is a Big Sink.
Big Sink or Power Sink, I wonder?
A brush, right?
Brush.
Ah.
You said so yourself.
Luxury.
The order's coming in.
Again today,
dishes.
By the way,
if you fail five times within that 155-minute window and get a game over,
can you restart from the beginning again?
I think you'd have to start over from the very beginning.
At that point,
do they at least give you credit for the highest day count you reached?
What happened last time?
I don't think they gave it to us last time.
Seriously? Then failing would really suck.
That means we absolutely must avoid failing, seriously.
Oh, thank you very much.
Maybe.
I've kind of forgotten the rules around here,
not sure exactly how it worked.
Alrighty!
If you get a game over,
that's it—yep, it's over. Done.
End of story. Scary.
Okay, good!
Alright, okay!
OK.
Ah, sorry.
This actually seems pretty great.
Can we make the window side wider?
With this layout, probably not.
Where's the window?
Um, that pass-through area here.
Ah, that wall there
can't be demolished, right? I see.
Like this,
Nice!
Amazing! Amazing! Sorry!
Now, about the sink,
What did the sink end up being?
Soak Sink.
It says 'Soak Sink'.
What's that?
Is this a Soak Sink?
Do we even need it?
Well, maybe it's not bad to have.
The Soak Sink automatically cleans dishes just by placing them inside it.
Before you know it,
though it takes a bit of time.
And since you can only place one dish at a time until it's clean,
I'm not sure.
I think it'd be better to just get an automatic dishwasher.
But how do we undo that?
Because I upgraded this sink to a painted one
Giving that on one hand
Because I upgraded this sink
After updating it
We'll end up back in Shokuzenki
We won't go back to Shokuzenki
There are two more types, and after that
Either one of the two Power Sinks?
It should become either a Big Sink or a Power Sink
Should I try upgrading again via gacha?
Might be worth a shot
Also, as long as Cookie Lis-chan isn't
Still finding it too difficult
Maybe I could add a few more tables
Pekora is handling the dining tables
I wonder if customers will start coming in
It feels a bit sparse
Actually, maybe not all tables were being used
We don't really need that many
If only we could just call
There's no phone to instantly fill up the place with customers
Well then, alright
Let's clear this once first
Then I'd like to try the version with the phone
Yeah, that's true—ah, peshi peshi
Peshi peshi peshi peshi peshi
I wonder what we'll get, I wonder what we'll get, tarara
Isn't that the one?
Could it be a Power Sink?
This was a good one, right?
I think the Power Sink is good too
Feels suited for RTM though—well, okay
Let's go right away
Let's buy it!
I'm gonna buy it!
More customers, please come
You can come even more, you know!
O-oh
Oh
Yosho—
Nice! Okay, good
Just need to get the plates
Here you go—I'll take your order!
Feeling good
Okay
Taking orders now!
Even without taking orders
It's definitely a burger
Oops
I want that
Alright
Careful
Customer
The number of customers is increasing
Indeed
Feels like it's getting busier
Thank you
Probably the last group
Cleaning
Please give me a tip
Earned money!
It's getting busier
Rich people—
Ah
Hmm
Well, either way is fine, I guess
If it were RTA
Would it not matter?
This one doesn't really matter either way
Yeah
Yes
Then
I'll buy this Power Sink! Yes!
Gambling
It's kinda expensive
Ah, but I guess we can afford it
Can we buy it here?
Buying it here
What exactly is a Power Sink again?
What was it again?
The Power Sink
Is the thing that makes dishwashing faster
If I use it with the brush
It probably finishes in a 'pew!'
That fast?
There are two sinks now.
All these different chandeliers hanging down...
Do you understand the effect of this?
It says it gives a luxurious feel.
That's right.
I think we picked something just now, between two options.
Which one to choose—this one here?
If we pick this one...
We can choose a buff effect, right?
There are three of them.
And now...
I'm not exactly sure what we just did.
Maybe it gives a slightly more luxurious vibe?
And now, diamonds...
Sometimes there's one diamond...
Sometimes three...
There are versions with diamonds attached.
These diamonds...
When three are attached, you get one buff...
That's how it works.
Yeah, there was one with three diamonds, right?
I can't afford to buy this sculpture.
It's too expensive—I can't buy it.
Not even that globe...
Or even one painting—I can't afford either.
But, you know...
In an RTA run, I don't think...
We really need to prioritize this stuff.
By the way...
This...
Floors and walls are free, so, well...
You can buy as much as you want.
Oh, really? Just hold X and...
You can buy them.
But I don't need them—I won't buy any.
It's just personal preference anyway.
So, this time...
Should we go with buying nothing at all?
Yeah, that sounds fine.
This...
Can these decorations be upgraded too?
No, these can't be upgraded.
Apparently, you can't do that.
OK! Let's go, let's go! Let's go!
Let's do our best again today.
Let's do our best! Let's do our best! Let's do our best!
Welcome! Welcome!
Two Ivys, right? Yes, okay!
And then cross the sky.
How's the Power Sink?
Whoa, so fast!
Right?!
Power Sink is awesome!
The best!
Hair—
Arai's hair has arrived!
No matter what happens, I won't be discouraged.
Badge...
Come on!
Ufufufu~
Oh no!
The shop is getting dirty... Plates without stains~
Ah!
Thank you very much!
Oh no!
The shop is getting dirty.
Sorry about that.
As for the character, that...
Can't be supported. Can't go outside.
It's too far away.
I don't need the normal evolution though...
So I guess it's better to evolve it after all.
Yeah, that's right.
If you get a Power Evolution on your first try, that's a win.
But that's just down to luck, huh?
From this side...
Super fast!
The fastest in the world—super fast!
It's like Germany's Autobahn!
Is it really that fast?
There's no speed limit or anything.
No speed limit.
So, there really isn't any limit?
That sounds dangerous.
That's probably why it's so popular.
There are actually quite a few people who want to drive in Germany.
That's fine, isn't it?
Two wonderful things.
I know it really well.
The viewers are getting upset.
The customers' patience meter is disappearing.
I think that's better.
Maybe it's better not to look.
Even if it disappears, isn't it not really causing any issues anymore?
It also feels kind of scary.
Because of the customers...
Wait, hold on!
They can't see that it's like this.
This might be bad.
Well, it'll probably be fine.
Maybe it'll work out.
Hmm, there's also something else I'd like to try.
Maybe we should try evolving it a bit.
Like evolving the dining table or something.
Can you really evolve a dining table?
Yes, you can.
This one here...
Anything marked as 'upgradable'...
...can all be upgraded.
What does it turn into?
Hey!
There are many different kinds of tables.
This one too.
OK.
Then...
Once it starts, I'll upgrade it.
Please do.
Welcome!
Elise, we don't need the stove anymore.
The stove is fine.
Again, it's fine—OK.
Leave it to me, please!
Once every 15 minutes...
...how much do you want to see?
Huh? What's this? You can't do it? It's the same as washing?
Washing and...
Huh?
I can't press anything.
Lag.
Pressed it.
Huh?
Lag, lag, lag—maybe...
Can't press rate.
I might need some plates.
Hold on a sec.
The response is...
It got laggy.
It became laggy.
So laggy.
Laggy—no way!
Pose.
Pose showing it's okay now.
OK.
One keyboard.
The misaligned button—that's what happened.
Kyura-san.
Excuse me, sorry about that.
Naked—full nudity assimilation! Full nudity assimilation!
Nobody's asking for that!
Huh?
People are asking for it—the chat wants it!
Hiara-chan.
The listeners might want it.
We need to clear these plates first.
Wake up the customers outside.
That cloud gauge, you know...
I want to wake up.
Try putting it down.
Oh no, it's getting busy—really busy!
Gotta take all the orders.
It's super busy!
Sorry, but the shop being messy is something you’ll have to forgive.
A bit of messiness actually makes it tastier—that's the basic rule.
With restaurants...
Anyway, I'm counting on you.
Deliciousness doesn't correlate with cleanliness.
Yeah, exactly, exactly!
Oh no, I missed an order!
Oh no, oh no, oh no—nice!
Nice! That was close!
Only dirt stays silent forever.
We need to clear that plate.
Nice, nice!
Nice!
Probably just one plate.
There's an extra one downstairs.
Clear the one downstairs.
Outside customers won't wait.
When they say they can't wait,
the gauge turns red, you know.
I see.
You know,
Outside customers won't wait.
When it says they can't wait,
maybe we should prioritize serving burgers to solo customers first.
There's only one plate left to clear anyway.
I get it.
Knowing this,
But I think we can go now.
Clear!
That was close, that was close!
It was really tight at the start.
So, about this—does this mean
we don't have to clean the dirty store anymore?
No, that's not right.
You know, earlier,
with that buff effect,
there's also a buff effect that prevents the store from getting dirty.
Oh, really?
Should we aim for that?
We’d probably be in trouble if we don’t clean.
But,
it’s super dirty.
There’s also an item that instantly cleans things up,
called a mop.
Oh, there’s something like that too.
That’s also based on luck,
whether it drops or not.
I wish we could get a mop.
Well then,
it might drop.
This Gas Rinnit thing,
looks pretty good,
doesn’t it look like Gasuri?
Eh, but
we don’t need it, right? We don’t need it.
Huh? Don’t need it? What did it turn into?
That dining table,
is a shared table.
We only need one of these, right?
Even if two people come,
it’s just about thinking time,
like at the very beginning, when they’re deciding
what to eat—that decision takes way too long.
I wonder how this would work in an RTA run.
Maybe it’s worth buying and trying it out once.
Yeah, let’s buy it.
We’ve got money anyway.
Might be a good idea.
Also,
earlier, about plates,
Suu mentioned plates,
actually,
you can pick them up diagonally.
Then,
we should just use Suu-ga.
Yeah, yeah, you can pick them up, you can pick them up.
Understood for worst-case scenarios.
Yeah, in worst-case scenarios,
even with walls, you can grab diagonally.
Ah, so even from farther away—I get it.
Huh?
I accidentally recorded some of our conversation.
Thanks.
Heave ho, heave ho.
Where should I put this?
It’ll end up far away.
Press B to pass through walls,
you know.
But let’s see,
within these 15 minutes,
how far we can get with our current skill.
Honestly, yeah.
Luck with gacha pulls probably matters too.
It’s really about whether we can reach Day Hatch or not.
With just 15 minutes...
If we have 15 minutes,
I guess we could probably make it around here.
That's what I think.
Personally, I’d say we’ve got plenty of time.
So, should we reset once?
Or should we just keep going with the hard one?
Just for a moment...
I also want to try that phone thing.
Honestly, Pekora...
Reservation...
Let’s do the reservation.
Could you reset it once for me?
Oh, and by the way—
There’s that catalog re-order option, right?
Down below...
This one exists.
You can do this for just 10 yen.
Give it a try.
What even is a catalog?
It’s useful when none of the items you want show up.
Yeah, exactly, exactly!
For example, like this—
You want a mop, but it doesn’t appear,
Like, um...
when something you really want just won’t show up,
as a last resort,
you spend 10 yen using this feature.
The gacha’s pretty nice.
Each time you use it, it adds 10 yen.
Seriously? It’s already 20 yen!
My recommendation is this plate stand.
The plate stand is actually quite good.
It holds four used plates.
You can put four dirty plates there—it’s super handy.
I really want it.
As for cleaning-related items...
I guess having somewhere to put dirty plates would help avoid situations where you can’t place them anywhere.
But...
When I was watching earlier,
there wasn’t really a spot for dirty plates,
so...
I didn’t really feel troubled by that much.
So maybe it doesn’t really matter either way.
Well then...
The absolute must-haves are definitely
the brush and Power Sink.
Yeah, that’s right.
Brush and Power Sink.
Speed Boots aren’t necessary.
What about that one above...
What’s on the top left?
Oh, takeout!
Also, if you put that on the table,
customers finish eating really quickly,
so they leave sooner.
It improves your table turnover rate.
However...
doing that means
you have to perform the extra task of placing it,
which the floor staff would have to handle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well...
it depends on whether it actually appears or not.
And...
there are all kinds of items,
so while speedrunning (RTA), try out different ones
and see which ones are the most efficient.
I think that’s worth testing.
Got it.
Reset.
Reset, reset!
Let’s start over from the beginning.
Normally, it appears by 8 o’clock.
Reservation.
Please also try the desk.
Going back to the main menu...
Yeah.
Once...
Let’s start from the beginning again.
Huh?
Can’t press video.
List! Yay, list!
Yay!
You know, Pekora is red.
What?
Um...
The chef's...
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Pekora red.
Ah, I see!
Why don't they just make it 'Pekora color'?
That's the one!
You can change it with mirrors and stuff.
You can change it right here.
Huh?
You can even add ears!
Wait a sec—don't be silly!
This color...
Like, colors and...
Stuff you put on your head and...
And also, which one exactly is the color?
Color refers to hats and clothes.
Kind of like that.
When you first pressed it, right?
There is one.
Hmm, there's no bar though.
There's no gacha either.
Well, there's no bar tomorrow anyway.
If it's not there, then... um...
The tutorial will handle it...
And then go back...
Gacha!
What's this called...
What a pain!
The menu's in the gacha, okay?
Ah, Pekora-senpai looks more like herself now!
I want to avoid looking too much like Suu-chan though...
It'd be hard to tell us apart otherwise.
If we have bunny ears...
And slightly different colors too...
Yeah, oh wow, that actually looks good! It's coming together!
Here it comes! Perfect color, okay!
We gotta do this first, though.
We don't need a tutorial.
She's dancing, so it's fine.
OK!
Please, burger, come out! Burger, come out!
Thank you!
Gold first, right?
Or wait, is it the phone?
Yeah, buy the phone.
C--U-D-D-L-E, right?
It's getting a bit easier.
It's starting to get fun!
It's getting kind of rural though...
Is that okay?
Ah, but this place is supposed to be city-like!
Watch out! Watch out! Nice!
Alright, from here on, it's the start.
Okay.
Reservation desk, please.
Ah...
So it starts right from here?
Right, this reservation desk...
Where should we put this?
Ah, here?
Maybe here?
Inside?
Yeah.
Ah, I get it.
But since I'm not using a Kiara controller...
Yeah, I wouldn't know.
I don't know the buttons—makes sense, right?
Do you wanna do the bookings or should I?
But in the beginning...
I think I can do it.
But later, I don't know who can do it.
Maybe I can do it because I've been making a lot of burgers.
Ah, no—yeah, okay. So if I have, like...
free hands... bread...
Mito Mito!
Because this initial prep is included too...
We gotta quickly stack the bread here—bam, bam, bam!
Right.
We gotta do it really fast.
Ah, I see now!
And, this is pressing B
I think the fastest way is to use the crane and just swing it around like that
Ah—
Not humans, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah
Alright, let's do it!
Hey, is that spot okay?
That sink
Ah— yeah, that's true
Alright, heave-ho, heave-ho
Let's give it a try—ring it!
Ring it! Ah, it’s 3 yen at first
How many times should we do it?
At the beginning, you know…
I think it’s fine to ring them all—every single one
Is there a limit?
Even if you keep ringing until the gauge at the top maxes out
I think it’ll be fine
It’s fine
You can ring even more
It’s totally fine—totally fine
Day One is totally fine
I think Day One is totally manageable
But
Everyone comes all at once
And yet
Should we ring all the phones right at the start?
Like, saying 'from the middle' or something
I think ringing them all at once right from the very beginning is best
And with this, all the customers will be
Once these people all leave
That’ll be the end of the day
It’s super fast, crazy fast, right?
We’ve already earned 45 yen!
Woo!
It’s getting laggy
Sara’s still not done—this is bad
Laggy Pekora’s fine
It’s fine
Once we surround that hamburger, it’s over
No way
Nice!
Heave-ho
Oh—
Nice! Hurry up
Buy the upgraded desk
Oh, that exists, exists, exists!
Because, press B, press B
It turns into a crane
And then carry it over
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah—also throw the sink right in there too
The sink too
Threw it in—threw it iiiin!
Now, take your positions—start!
Okay! Ah, it’s lagging now
Yeah
This is bad right now
Is it OK?
Fixed
This thing
The crane
Um…
It won’t start unless this turns into a human
Ah—
This
Was B finished?
Ah—already done
Oh no
Laggy Pekora
Laggy Pekora has arrived
Oh no
Ah, really—it might be a bit laggy
Come on, Power Sink!
Is it Power Sink?
Or Soaking?
Why?
Huh?
Don’t we need to ring it?
Yeah, I really forgot
More, more, more
Is this okay?
It makes you nervous, huh?
Hold onto Sana—it’s super cramped
Already at the limit
This is day two.
After this...
I guess we'll finish with the two groups outside.
Easy.
We're starting to run out of plates.
What part of the water is slippery?
Yes.
Ah, they still haven't noticed.
You're the one who's slippery.
Looked at oil and water.
Oil is hard to walk on. OK, got it.
OK, th—
—is way.
Alright.
So, will these two people finish first?
OK, yes.
Thank you for the meal.
OK.
OK, OK.
OK, OK, that's fine.
That's fine.
Hurry, hurry! Press the A button here too!
Shinka, what did you become?
It's a pre-soak single.
An unnecessary brush has arrived.
Brush, brush!
Nice, nice! The best!
Thank you very much.
You're a lifesaver.
We don't need anything else.
I wanted to ask about this...
When I checked the upgraded version, it looked different.
At that time, even if I spent 10 yen on the gacha...
That part won't change.
It might turn into something completely different.
It probably has nothing to do with sinks or anything.
I see, okay, okay, okay.
The lag is terrible right now, just a bit.
I have a meeting starting around 9:30.
I'll take my leave around here.
Thanks a lot!
Congratulations!
Do your best!
Understood.
Good thing the area manager came.
Pecolos wasn't hacked, after all.
That's true.
Oh no!
Down below.
Nice!
Should we go down this way?
Please! Please!
Okay, here we go!
We need some plates, somehow.
Hey, are they showing up? Maybe we're short on plates.
Also...
That's true.
But washing them...
...should still be manageable.
Barely.
If we're fast enough, we won't even need plates.
Couples aren't coming anymore.
Looks like couples aren't showing up.
It's probably because of the reservation over there.
I see, that makes sense.
OK, maybe that's fine then.
Day 3, OK.
OK.
Victory.
Press A here quickly, right here—
Right here, once per day—
Huh?
What does 'use the desk once per day' even mean?
Well, anyway...
...we've got no other choice but this.
What's a desk?
Desk.
Reservation desk.
That's not it, right?
I don't get it. What's going to happen?
Well, anyway...
...this time slot is still within the 15-minute window, so...
...just do it randomly.
For now, we gotta throw in some bread quickly.
This is bad, right?
Someone get it!
No
Is it Pekora or...?
Seriously?
This one, the upgrade thing
Wanna look?
I just synced ahead
Ah, let's buy a sink, this one
Dining table
Ah, isn't that the Power-whatsit?
Let's just buy it
Let's buy it—Pret too, I guess
Is it okay if I buy it?
Like, next time or something
If we do an upgrade or something
Wouldn't you suddenly max it out all at once?
Probably not, right?
Next time, I'll try upgrading
Should I give it a shot once?
What will it become? Okay!
Okay
It turned out awesome
Getting better
Hehehe
And again
Because of Pekora's lag
Pekolag
Here comes Pekolag
Pekolag Un! Here it comes, here it comes!
Hmm, I upgraded it, but
I don't know what it became—OK!
Ris
Previously upgraded the herb
Come on, come, come
Come on, come on
Not there
Normally I use herbs
Pekora-senpai, Pekora's in trouble
I can't even handle my own lag anymore
This is crazy, crazy, crazy
Crazy, crazy
Alright, okay
Thank you very much
Ah, forgot
Power Brush, Scrap Brush, Scrap, Scrap
Scrap, scrap, scrap
Scrap
Like
Even more so on that side
If that's the case
If you could put it closer on this side
I feel like I could do it whenever I want
A dog holding hands
Is Pekora, the lag user, going now?
It might be turning into something like that
Everyone's moving weirdly
It's fine, we can still do it, Suu-chan
I'm covering for you, right?
We'll keep going
Sorry about that
Pekora's moving weirdly though
That's bad
Send it over, please
Everyone's on international teams
Does everyone have lag?
That's true
No
Pekora's already trying to wrap things up
Suzui-chan's handling everything
So that's why this is happening
Seriously, why does it always end up like this with me?
I've always thought this about this guy, yeah
Maybe I already messed up
Right there, Pekora-senpai
Isn't it over there? Faster
Before I knew it
Aku and Pekora don't even know who that is
Because they're fighting Lagzo
Seriously?!
Ah, um
Became Safety Hope
Ah, getting late kinda sucks
But it won't burn
Hey, what's going on?
Maybe we don't need Risu-chan.
We don't need her, nope, don't need her.
Okay, okay!
Seems fine as it is.
Let's give it a try.
If there's a Safety Hoop,
I'd like them to upgrade it.
I really want to do it again, honestly.
Let's try it once more.
Maybe something good will come along.
That was quick.
OK.
Yes! Here it comes, here it comes!
Solo player.
Let them in first.
So fast!
Oh, so quick!
Oh, quickly—good!
Yeah, oh, quickly—going down!
Going down, yep—going down!
Is it really okay to go this fast?
It's fine, yeah!
These two are off, aren't they?
Oh no!
Wait!
Like this—and yes!
Stop it quickly!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Huh?
Logging in...
Ah—
Oh no!
Dug dug! Everyone, Dug—it's bad!
Everyone, dug dug dug!
It's bad—I can't grab it!
Come on, come on!
Quickly, okay!
Okay, it might be over, it might be over!
Might be game over now.
I see...
Actually feels pretty good.
What levels are you guys at?
Where can you check your level?
Ah, I'm level 6 right now—level 6!
Oh, then...
This bottom-right corner...
Uh, um, here—right here!
It doesn't show the level here.
Mine says 6 too, though.
Ah, Pekora also says level 6.
Everyone's around the same level.
Eh? What about Risu-chan?
I'm 6—huh?
Then we're the same.
What's Disen-senpai's level?
Maybe?
I see...
How do you even check your own level?
We might need to disband once.
To raise our own levels,
let's disband once
and then make a room together again.
Apparently, we all get experience points.
We don't get them right now,
but we'll get them after disbanding, it seems.
What should we do?
Shall we disband once?
We could stay like this, but...
Level 6 is just right anyway,
so we can make hamburgers.
But, you know, on the day itself,
even if it ends up like this, there's nothing we can do.
Because...
it's happening worldwide.
If Su-chan or Pekora
or the senpai reaches level 6,
either of them can open a room,
which might make things a bit better.
But that might make Kiara-chan or
Risu-chan even more laggy, I think.
Someone will probably lag.
I feel like Cook is important.
Maybe it's still best to have Rissu-chan do it after all.
Rissu-chan is the best.
It just means it's easier to create in an environment that's more comfortable for me, right?
That wouldn't be bad either, though.
If we try it once with just the Japanese members,
we might actually see whether there's lag or not.
Maybe...
Fa—
n—
Members
Oh no!
The speed-up itself just dropped.
So like this,
Lip Trio
OK
Ah—
And then, again, that thing...
I wonder what level it's at now.
Huh? This hasn't leveled up at all!
Th-th-th-that th-th-th-that
Is it the one you get when you leave the room?
Maybe it's level 1.
No way!
I've
leveled up.
I went up to level 3.
Yeah, it went up to level 3.
Look over there.
Next to the tutorial on the left,
aren't some points dropped there?
Points—wait a sec.
Tutorial
There should be something dropped next to the tutorial.
I see.
Hmm, but since we're still only level 3,
we probably don't have enough yet, right?
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
We probably need around level 4 or so.
OK, then
I'll still rely on Rissu-chan, okay?
That's our only option. Sorry.
Could you call her again?
Pekoran
Please check out our Instagram!
Thank you!
Next time,
maybe we should properly time ourselves and try it.
Like, how many stages we can clear in 15 minutes,
that sounds good.
Should we time it?
Yeah, that sounds like a good idea.
Instagram is ready.
Yes.
I'm back.
Shu-chan, should we time it?
Right now, the timer thing—
Thanks, there's no bar.
How do we check that again?
Gacha, maybe?
The timer thing—
How did we look it up again?
Timer
Timer or stopwatch—
Thank you very much.
There are only three people.
Huh?
Hm?
Ah, sorry.
Pekorea
Ki—
—e
There's no burger, huh?
Nope—not here! Here I am!
What are you gonna do about this?
Again?
Guccho, maybe?
Okay.
Aki was kinda far away.
Oh!
Why are you outside?
Eh, something's wrong!
Are you in another world or something? Hey!
Wait, what?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Don't go in!
Why outside
I wonder why
Huh? Not there
Huh? It's not coming out at all?
Suddenly, I
Why?
Ah, it means I should properly do the tutorial
That's what it means
Sakanaa
Ah
There's Burgan, there's Burgan
Nice, nice
Niiice
Hamburger, and then
I guess I need to put in another seed
Still know it
Know it
OK
Beautiful
Yeah!
Then, once Suu-chan joins later
Wait a moment, please
In that case
I'll measure it with my phone. Ah, but
To the embassy
Made it
Yay!
Is the room invite coming?
Joining the room from Riss-chan
Only the color gets in
This isn't the real Suu-chan
Made it darker. Good, good
OK OK OK
Alright
How far can we get in 15 minutes?
It's already been four hours since start
Ah, okay, start
Button bububu, okay
And, uh, it's Boking, Boking
Can be put into the machine
Well
Maybe it's fine to walk here, but
This is important again
Hmm
I'll put it here for now
Nikkey Arabao Okay
This one also doesn't have 15 minutes left, right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes
It's 14 minutes and 21 seconds now
Let's go
This should work
Here it comes
It's here! It came, it came!
Burger's ready—it's already nighttime
Okay
Burger bar
Gar burger bar
Gar burger
Oh no
What happened?
It's bad, seriously bad already
Already bad
What happened?
People passed by too quickly
Lag
No
Probably just not enough seats
Ah, maybe booking a bit earlier
Probably
We need to move one person first
Maybe that's it
Ah, I see
Chiri chiri, chirin
When you do that, you can't go anymore
Then
One person gets priority
Initially, it's better if all reservations are filled
Didn't someone say something like that? Is it okay?
It's fine
Take this first
Do it like this
Ya
Baiya
Baiya bai
Oh no
It's okay
Whoa, they're hitting!
They're hitting
They're overcoming it
It's okay, they're overcoming it
The plate I grabbed
is back on the desk where it was originally
What’s going on?
Well
Anyway, nice, nice
Nice, nice
Nice—what’ll come out?
Sink, sink
Upgrade
Desk Mario upgrade
Can I put it here?
Um
With the floating one
Please, thank you
Thank you, thank you—put it
First, this one
Okay, okay, okay
Okay
Good, good
Alright, let's go
Power Sink, come on
Yeah, we really need that Power Sink
Ah
It got on the dishwasher—I don't want it
Yes, here it comes, here it comes
Pekora, oh no
That
Seriously, this is bad
Right now, there's Pekora from Razsky
Wait, okay okay, hold on
This is already bad
Nothing’s staying in Pekora’s hands anymore
Okay, okay
They won’t take it
This plate
Oh no, oh no, oh no
Already
I’m always holding a plate with no burger
Put that down
I’ve got the burger
Pekora’s got it, got it, got it
Alright, alright
Done, done
Seriously, Pekora, oh no, oh no, oh no
Plate, please, plate
Plate, please
Wait, hold on
Oh no, oh no—it’s over
What are they gonna say?
Nukari-senpai, put that down, Nukari-senpai
Put that down—where, where?
Where?
Hard mode, huh
Then it’s a challenge
Ah, but things are getting smoother—oh no
Showed it
Huh?
Yes yes yes yes ah
Oh no, oh no, oh no
The person at bottom left is angry
OK, OK
OK
Going, going
Hey
I can’t do this
Can I make it unreadable?
Fukashima’s holding it, holding it
Hold it—give it to someone
Give it to someone—ah, kekeke
Hold this, hold this
Got it, OK OK OK OK
Successfully handed it off
Already handed it over
Handed it off—only holding the burger
Ah, not holding it now
Right now, I’m not holding anything
Pekora, here it comes, here it comes
That’s Pekora-senpai
There’s a box at bottom right
Why a burger?
Plate, please. A plate.
A dirty plate.
A dirty plate... but maybe it's fine now?
Ah—
I still want one more after all.
OK OK OK, oh no, right now—
I have no idea what Pekora is even looking at or doing.
Go ahead, go ahead!
Thank you so much! Made it just in time—
OK, got it!
This is bad—the world everyone else sees
and the world Pekora sees are way too different!
Pekora’s gone off the rails!
I don’t even know what that was, but...
What she’s doing is actually kind of nice.
It’s already over before I knew it.
This is scary...
I think I’ll just move on to the next thing.
Or maybe...
I could reroll with Blue Prince, but...
We got a sink!
Should we do the sink?
But, since we already entered the sink...
it didn’t give us the item we wanted.
Alright then, let’s—
Let’s go!
But...
Brush hasn’t dropped yet, either...
Wait, right now—
There might’ve been a Multi Brush!
Huh?
No way!
It’s over already?!
But, Power Sink...
is probably definitely not it.
Soaking again—but it’s not the item I wanted.
Okay.
This is bad—I can’t get it no matter what!
I’m getting it! I’m getting it!
When luck’s bad, you end up stuck with Low-Low, like, Low-Low...
There! Right there, right there!
From my perspective, that unlock is necessary.
Right now, right now, Senpai Pekora—
is holding a dirty plate—a dirty plate, seriously?!
Don’t mess with me!
I don’t get it!
This...
That’s another dirty plate!
Senpai Pekora, please put that back!
She was supposed to be holding a burger, but...
somehow turned into a dirty plate instead.
Before I even realized...
Another dirty plate!
What’s going on?! Did someone put this here?!
Seriously, Senpai Pekora...
I think she’s drunk.
No, it’s not that—
The world Bekora sees
is just slightly different from what everyone else sees—it’s insane!
Fukura-senpai, you’re in the way!
Plate!
You’re blocking the way!
I get it, I get it!
She was trying her best, really trying!
Brush! Brush! Brush! Brush! Brush!
Please! This one, this one, this one, this one!
It ended before I even noticed!
Amazing!
I just moved the sink by accident.
Ah, there actually is a Multi-Brush!
Nice! Nice!
Nice!
Shall we go?
Yes.
Let’s go.
Since I accidentally moved the sink just now...
I’ll leave just the sink positioning to you.
Got it.
OK here.
Let's go.
Right now, I'm going blind,
so I barely even know what I'm thinking myself.
Just tell me what you're thinking.
You'd probably say something like, 'Please stay down there.'
The world has somehow moved way too far ahead,
and turned into a scary future—yeah, that's right.
Even Senpai Pekora isn't around.
She went to see a customer,
so I thought, 'Yeah, that must be it.'
Huh?
Can you get two soaking sinks in a row?
You're holding a plate right now, aren't you?
Is this a plate?
Is this a burger?
Maybe you're not holding it right now.
You're holding a burger now.
Where should I go?
This way?
Senpai Pekora!
There's no plate.
Looks like we're out of plates.
You're holding it now.
Not holding it.
Senpai Pekora just spoke.
Up! Senpai Pekora, up!
Up!
This one.
This guy.
Dirty plate.
This is a dirty plate.
Sou-chan, are you okay?
This is kinda tough.
Oh no!
Ah—
Ahahahaha!
Busy, huh? Why?
Why did it turn out like this?
Why, Pekora?
Why has my world line diverged so much from everyone else’s already?
This...
But why though?
Maybe this happened because...
It fell,
so maybe things got a bit worse again?
Yeah, maybe that's it.
Like this...
Ah, we don't need the dishwasher!
Ah, the dishwasher!
No no, I want to power sink.
Akki!
I'll let them know.
To Senpai Pekoro.
Pekora, you know...
Has the waitress gotten worse?
I wonder if Sou-chan's burden is okay.
That’d be insane, right?
It's fine!
Senpai Pekoro, you're holding it, holding it!
Senpai Pekoro, put that down below.
You're holding this, yes, holding it, holding it!
You handed it over.
Delivered!
Ah—I gave it; you're not holding this anymore.
But you've been holding it the whole time...
Pekora, like, burgers and stuff...
You managed to hand it over—you’re giving it now!
Hold it once more.
Hold it again, Senpai Pekoro!
Holding it, holding it!
Please give it to just one person.
One person hasn’t come yet, hasn’t come!
Here, here—top left!
Top left, top left—is it here?
Right here.
You're handing it over—perfect!
Senpai Pekuro!
You took the burger.
Not holding it.
Not holding it, not holding it.
This is Burger-senpai.
I want you to hand it over right there, right there, right there, right there.
Here, okay?
I handed it over, right there, right there, right there.
It's handed over, handed over, perfect!
Perfect! Okay, okay, okay!
Good, good, good!
Our communication streak is getting really impressive.
I took this burger.
Can't hold it.
Do your best!
I took this.
Already holding a plate—plate, dish!
That's a plate, yeah! Yay!
What is this? I want to do it!
Can't proceed.
Can't proceed from Day-san.
Huh? Why?
Ah, is it just one person? Or maybe that...
Though there actually weren't that many people.
Now...
Wait, the game isn't over yet, right?
It's over.
But it's not over yet.
Ah, but we still have time.
We still have 2 minutes and 40 seconds left.
No, that's not what I meant.
I meant, we're still making burgers, right?
We're not making any.
Pekora-senpai, it's over.
Right now?
That part is finished.
Pekora, you're delivering burgers right now.
Burgers.
The ones on the table—the kitchen ones.
Where should I take it?
But I feel like I'm supposed to be holding a task item or something.
You're not holding anything.
Pekora, it's not over yet.
There's no such thing as game over.
World War is quite different, actually.
Pekura-senpai left me behind.
We lost just now—it reset.
It's super slow.
Feels like a significant delay.
This is bad, seriously.
Yeah, this is kinda bad.
Seriously, just a bit...
We should probably re-invite them.
But this is really bad.
At this point, maybe we should leave once and...
...get re-invited back in?
Goodbye.
Can you re-invite someone while the game is already started?
Didn't you say earlier...
Was it re-invite after the game started?
Pekari-senpai, you're holding it now, holding it!
Holding it!
Went downstairs, downstairs!
Nice! Nice!
In situations this bad...
...you really should just rejoin the room.
Probably, ultimately...
Pekora-senpai, can you hold that?
Alright, got it!
That's pretty nice, right there!
Placed it, placed it—perfect!
Perfect!
If a burger appears in front of Pekora...
...let me know.
Can hold it now.
Multitasking!
Wow, Pekora's amazing at this!
If there's a burger here, tell Pekora—it's right in front of her.
Not yet.
Wait, Pekora-senpai!
The plate—
Yes!
It's fine now—I've got it!
Got it now!
Downstairs—ah!
Downstairs.
Ah, but...
Already handed it over.
Over here
Now
I went, I went
I went
Perfect!
Good, good
Good
Ah, you can hold it, you can hold it, Senpai Pekora
Now
You can hold it
Uh-uh, can't hold it
You can hold it, right?
OK
I'll hold it—I held it
Probably
Around here
It's being placed
Nice, nice
Are you moving based on future prediction?
That's insane
You can hold it
These two
It's fine to place it
Placed it
Can hold it now
Up
Nice!
The timer just rang
Where?
15 minutes over
But if there were no lag, that'd be right
If there were no lag
Pekora and the others could make it
Pekora and the others, go down—right now, down
Not there, to the right of that—over here
But we can place it, we can place it
Kani
Suu-chan's
If you peek at Suu-chan's screen showing the threat, Pekora could do it, right?
Not by myself
Suu-chan's screen sharing
Maybe we can manage if we look at the screen share
We're doing it right now
Pekora's game isn't over yet
Sales figures haven't shown up either
But when looking at Suu-chan's screen
The sales numbers are showing up big time
Yeah, it's definitely over now
By the way, it's
Alright to relax now
Yeah, OK
But let's reset the timer once more
Start it from the beginning
And redo the room too
Shall we rebuild it?
Hopefully Senpai Pekora's lag gets fixed too. Yeah, OK
Then let's go back
Safe & Return or Abandon—
Safe & Return, let's do this once
Pekora will restart the game. Okay!
Okay!
Huh? Huh?
Plate upgrades happening so often it's ridiculous
Restarting
Why is the lag so bad though?
Hey
It's weird
Ah, level 6
Or not?
Ah, this is probably Senpai Kiara's level
Kiara-san
Seriously, Senpai Risu?
Yeah
Yeah yeah yeah, Risu-chan
Call me once more
Yes
Alright, thanks, Banger
Like this, then
Hope this fixes things
Sometimes there's no lag
But sometimes it suddenly gets heavy
How strange
Feels like it popped up due to a seed value
This
Pecoland Brazil
Maybe they really are on the other side
Huh, none of them are here
Isn't this supposed to be a four-person room? Huh?
Maybe it'd be better if you called me once again, huh? Yeah, okay.
Hey, sorry, could you call me once more?
Yeees!
Thank youuu!
Will this work to get in?
Huh?
It won't go in.
It's pitch black in here.
No way!
Oh no no no no!
Should we rebuild the entire room?
For now...
Ah, Risu!
It might as well be a completely new room. Yeah, yeah.
Maybe it's better to do it room by room.
Okay!
Wait a sec—!
Thank you!
I wonder how high the level will go.
Level...
Still only level 3, still level 3... Man, that's slow.
Just how much more do I have to do?
Still only level 3...
With this...
I'll go think about it.
Thank you very much!
Thanks a lot!
Please do your best!
That would really help. Well, that's about it for now.
Pekora-senpai...
For this year's soccer World Cup...
Are you rooting for Argentina?
Nah...
I'm also supporting Japan, but still...
Argentiiina...
I wonder what'll happen.
But still, go Japan!
Yeah, that's true, but...
Austria's group this time...
Their first opponent is Argentina, actually.
Oh, really?
I'm scared... I hope Austria wins, though.
I might need you to call me again.
Guess I should just leave once... Oh no, bad idea!
The color alone is scary like this.
Argentina won the last tournament, right?
If I recall correctly...
Hmm...
They're way too good.
Is Japan's team any good?
If only Japan were good enough...
I really don't wanna face Argentina.
Honestly speaking...
Right?
Everyone feels that way.
Good, good.
Ah!
Oops!
Let's change the color.
Huh, is this already looking good?
This...
Is it lagging?
I wonder if this room won't lag.
Everyone, please read my misunderstanding~!
Yes!
Injury... Are Japanese team members injured?
Yeah, yeah!
Seems like quite a few are injured.
Is this bad? If...
What if they don't heal? They will heal.
By then...
I hope they recover in time.
Who's the best player on the Japanese national team?
Who is it?
I think they're all really good.
Still...
But...
Watching soccer, especially Pe-kola, I always think...
I never want to be a goalkeeper.
The pressure from the press is just too intense.
Yeah, exactly—it's a huge responsibility too.
Whether or not you can stop it...
If you can't stop it...
That directly leads to conceding a goal.
Every single time with the goalkeeper...
I always end up watching while thinking, 'You can do it!'
Honestly...
Hey, um... whoa, wait, Pekora!
It's starting to lag from this point onward.
Movement-wise, is everyone okay?
Worst case, should we screen-share?
Yeah, worst case.
I'll screen-share.
Might not be working.
Huh? Were you already in the room?
Kubo?
Just joined now.
Seriously?
Then let's start the 15 minutes now.
Ah, starting right now, got it.
Start!
Alright,
Please handle the reservation desk.
And this...
Huh?
Suu-chan's handling it for us.
OK, nice! Just like this.
Shinku!
The door's hard to see. Wasn't it here?
Was it here?
I think it was this end and that end. OK.
Then this spot should be fine.
Oh no!
It's already lagging before we even started—no way!
Done!
Seriously, let's get the Japanese members to make a hair conditioner.
Yeah, true.
Might not be possible today, though.
Okay, let's go!
Let's do this!
Yes.
I'm fine.
Let's start.
Please go ahead with the reservation!
Actually,
It might be better to watch Suu-chan's screen,
Feels like it's still a few seconds too early.
In that case,
Hair...
Thanks, seems like it's around here.
Ah, I have it now, I have it now!
Ah, I can hand it over now!
I have it now.
It's working out!
Ah, different face now.
Heave-ho!
Ah, that one's on top!
Pekora-san, the top one!
OK, OK!
Please give it to just one person.
Ah, OK!
Ah, sorry, sorry, sorry!
It's totally fine!
Ah, with Pekora's thing, just one person...
Ah, that one has no plate.
Please spare me already!
I can't do anything!
I'm alright, Daikan-senpai!
I'm holding that.
Ah, I'm holding the hamburger now.
Ah, that one has no plate.
This is getting bad!
Don't think it's sour!
I can hold that.
That edge, edge, edge—ah, OK!
This is kinda bad.
I'm not even a spy!
Pekora's seriously going all out!
There are no customers right now, Pekora-senpai.
Nope, none.
OK.
OK, OK!
I wonder why...
The first 30 minutes or so
were going really well,
but now it won't fix itself—that update...
Ah, it's showing up.
Showing up, this one.
The beginning's already over.
It's finished already.
Still working hard, though, Pekora.
It's definitely moving right now.
Amazing, Senpai Pekora!
Pekora's holding us back.
Even though I came on skates...
Well...
Right now, press Y.
Waiting for the start.
I'm pressing Y already—it's started!
It's started!
Senpai Pekora, what's going on right now?
She's still playing My Game.
Still on My Game.
I'll check Suu-chan's screen.
You're popular right now!
Senpai Pekora...
If you don't move yourself...
It's impossible to tell how things are moving.
Oh no, I finally got into the game—
My Game ended, and everyone's rushing around getting ready!
Oh no!
This might be pretty slow.
Why am I stuck in this other dimension?
All by myself...
Why is only Senpai Pekora...
So far behind?
Hey, Suu-chan's support is getting really good!
Reliable!
Here it comes—
This way?
I need a plate.
Here you go.
Wait a sec—
Here it comes—
Buka-senpai, that one!
Put it there, please—right there!
Nice, nice, right here!
Ah, placed it, placed it!
Ah!
Buka-senpai, the bottom left one!
OK, okay!
Alrighty!
Luca, Shaba, bottom!
Bottom!
Now!
This way!
That one, bottom right!
Please take it to the bottom right!
Okay, okay!
Okay, okay, okay!
Good, good!
Great! Got it!
Oh!
Then...
Perfect!
Clearing now—waiting for the A button!
Senpai Pekora's still in the middle of it, but...
Pressed the A button!
Thank you!
Exiting—brush brush!
Oh, please,
My beloved brush!
Seriously, why was only Pekora...
So far ahead? Alright!
OK!
Brush!
What did it become?
Oh, King Sink!
No, no, no, no—okay!
Next!
This one—okay from before!
Okay!
Okay, thank you!
Ah!
I think I got the one I needed.
Ohhh!
Did it! Uh, leftmost!
Leftmost, okay!
Thank you!
Mama-chan!
Pekora-tachi are like this, huh?
Even when lag happens,
They're learning they can still communicate like this.
Tetsuya-senpai, that one—bottom left, okay!
Bottom left, got it.
Alrighty!
Ah, sorry!
Resolation is
yoisho, yoisho
yoisho
OK
Nice!
Forgot the brush
Brush
Forgot to use the brush, the brush
Do your best
Brush
There was a brush
There was
Nice!
Senpai Pekori
OK, OK
OK
While watching Suu-chan's screen share
I'm looking at the future world, so do your best
Luca Sebasle top-left
Top-left, right
This one, go ahead
There was one in Flash Brazil
Yes, I can hold it
That one, bottom-right
OK
Feeling good, feeling good
Luca Sebasle bottom-left
Nice!
OK
Here you go
Also
Only top-left, so
Ah, it hasn't arrived yet
Okay with Senpai Pekora
It came
OK
Well then
Right now, I can still hold it with the one below
Maybe one below
The one below—ah, yes
Here
Ah
In the back
Oh
OK
Good, using Pekoro like that is also great
You're getting better
You're doing well
Even in moments like this, it's a bit reassuring
And we got 4—nice!
Right now, they're using Eg-Pekoro really well
Yeah, but
You're actually doing quite well
Now, it's either right or left
Senpai Pekoro
Right or left—please go right
I'll wait—okay!
So
This is
Power
Braits
They're holding something
What
Please place that with X
Somewhere
X or A
Thank you very much
Placed it, placed it
Alright
Yes
Fully prepared—OK
We'll go by voice call
Apply the brush
One person at bottom-right—yes, bottom-right
Nice!
One person at top-left—yes, exactly
Yes, holding a burger
Holding it now
Holding it
Holding it at bottom-left
One person—right now
Left
In the back—there, there, nice!
Great—even with a handicap
It's good that you've gotten this skilled
Nice! If you need anything, just say so
Become even more like a god
No, that's right—Pekora, this is it
If everyone entered the same world
This would already break
This game
Yes, yes, exactly
I see, I can hold it
Pekoshi can hold it too
Can hold it
I can hold it
Right now, I might want you up top once
Bottom right
Top
Sorry, Pekoshi
Below that
Can hold it now
Go, go, go!
Pekoshi, hold it once more
Hold it again, there, there, there
Might not be able to hold it again
Held it
I held it—I could hold it, right?
Sorry about that
Kaiko
It's going well
Ruka-senpai, right now
You're only holding a plate
This is a plate
That's a plate, so
Put it down once
Ah, so it's like this
Last person, go for it!
Last is cleaning
Don't need it? Okay, okay, okay
Cleared!
Eh, already standing up?
Please
Sorry about that
After taking care of Pekora, I'm totally worn out
We still have about 3 more minutes
Hey
Come on, come on, come on—dangerous stove
The burner's igniting
Ah
It's fast, but the burner igniting is dangerous
I don't think we need the stove
OK
Regular ones are fine
Seriously, just cleaning stuff is enough, right?
Huh? What's this—it's already started?
It's started! It's started!
Haven't been able to hold it yet
It's okay
Can hold it now
MeguMasep, you can hold it now
Please put it in the bottom left, bottom left
These two members with two items are way too convenient
Way too OP
MeguMasep, you can hold it now—nice!
Nice! It's working!
It's working
OK OK
Seriously respect... umm
Pekora-san, top left—there, there, there! Nice!
But hey
We were supposed to give instructions to Pekora and Su-chan
Next, take that and go to the bottom right
Ah, bottom right—got it, bottom right
This way, right?
Thank you
Su-chan's gotten incredibly good at taking care of Pekora
Unbelievably skilled
This is crazy
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So, can I just go to the top left like this?
Ah, it's fine, it's fine
Like this, bottom left
Okay
Huh? Oh, I get it now
Clear!
Ah
wwwww Wait, what?
Ah, no—it was just me clearing it
I only cleared it myself
Ah, oh no
Wait
This...
Pekora can't move right now!
Right now, I'm holding a dirty plate.
Pekora-san...
Ah, okay, okay, okay, like this...
Purun~
Ah, yoi-sho! Ara-ra-ra-ran!
Hey!
Senior Pekora...
Um...
Right, right—ah, um, upper left, upper left!
Upper left!
Ah!
Wait a sec—oh no, oh no!
Ah, sorryy~!
It's over~!
It's done—it's all over~!
Seriously?!
Sorry, I used Pekora's thingy~
It's alright!
But did we make it to around day 5?
Right now...
If we managed to reach around day 5 with this lag...
The moment Pekora truly has no more lag...
We could definitely get into the top 8!
But thanks to Senior Pekora's lag...
I feel like I've gotten way better!
I really feel like I've improved a lot!
Yeah, that's true~
Though it'd still be better without lag~
What should we do, then~?
But honestly, even if we keep going like this right now...
It wouldn't count as proper practice, and I feel bad about that~
No, no, not at all!
Then let's do it again sometime!
If you have time later...
Maybe we could gather again privately or something...
Yeah, that sounds good—I really want to!
Let's practice properly today!
The lag seems pretty bad too...
So let's wrap it up for now...
And definitely do it again when our schedules align!
Thank you so much!
Let's work hard on team coordination, okay?
Let's do our best and win!
We won't lose to lag!
Pekora, you do your best too—let's win!
Let's win—let's go for victory!
Well then...
For the last one, on the count of three—what should we say?
On three: 'We will absolutely win!'
Let's aim for 1st place! That's it—long, loooong...
We will absolutely win!
Aim for 1st place! Loong, loooong...
On three: 'We will absolutely win!'
Aim for 1st place!
All over the place...
Bye-bye!